welcome everyone hi from my sides
欢迎大家在我身边打招呼
welcome to the webinar on spring from a
欢迎从春季参加网络研讨会
photo though actually covering even the
虽然实际上覆盖了照片
state of the immediately upcoming photo
即将发布的照片​​的状态
that one release so you get the very
那个版本，所以你得到
very latest here for the DOE that one is
这是DOE的最新消息
scheduled for release on Mondays which
预定在星期一发布
is in in a few days here and there's a
几天后在这里，有一个
note or two that I actually specific to
我实际上特定于的一两个便笺
for one even in this very presentation
即使在这个演讲中
here but fundamentally we're covering
在这里，但从根本上讲
the spring filmic full generation which
春季电影完整版
is well the fourth major generation of
是第四代
spring to begin with its in particular
春天特别从它开始
the first time if we really raise the
第一次，如果我们真的提高
baseline here after the spring framework
Spring Framework 之后的基线
three the door release we spent quite a
三门释放我们花了相当多的时间
bit of time with spring from a trio the
三人组与春天的时间
Frio line we introduced Spring Framework
Frio系列我们介绍了Spring Framework
3.1 with very significant new features
3.1具有非常重要的新功能
back then and we kind of ended that line
那时我们有点结束那条线
with a three to two generation which is
三到两代
still actively maintained spring thermic
仍积极保持春季热
for presents an opportunity for us to
为我们提供了一个机会
basically revisit the entire framework
基本上重新审视整个框架
and this is what this webinar is about
这就是本次网络研讨会的内容
really I'm going to explain a little bit
真的我会解释一下
about the motivation a little bit about
关于动机的一点
our our kind of mission here what are we
我们在这里的使命是什么
focusing on what are we driven by and
专注于我们所驱动的
I'm also going to to specifically
我也要专门
explain a few things about about
解释一些关于
upgrading plication
升级程序
so this is as much about introducing
所以这与介绍有关
spring from mokoro the framework itself
源于mokoro框架本身
as it is also about introducing spring
因为它也是关于引入弹簧的
framework for releases to your
发布到您的框架
deployment environments to your
部署环境到您的
development environments and your
开发环境和您的
deployment environments
部署环境
since we really went the extra mile to
因为我们真的付出了额外的努力
make sure that it's a smooth upgrade
确保升级顺利
from spring from extruder to in
从春季到挤出机
particular definitely consider that
特别肯定地认为
upgrade we'll revisit this to what's the
升级，我们将重新审视这是什么
end of the webinar first of all let's
网络研讨会的结束首先，让我们
just look where it's actually where it's
只是看看它实际在哪里
actually positioned in our portfolio
实际位于我们的投资组合中
these days
这些日子
spring fabric furrow is the foundation
春季面料沟是基础
of many things that we do in particular
我们特别要做的许多事情
it's the foundation for what we call the
这是我们所谓的基础
spring oil platform which will see its
春季石油平台将看到
first release in actually not not far
第一次发布实际上不远
out at all from here springtime ik
从这里春天出来
furrow is the easy foundation layer has
沟是容易的基础层
many pieces on top the next generation
下一代顶级产品
of Grails running on top of spring
Grails运行在春天的顶部
tomorrow our spring boot initiative
明天我们的 spring boot 计划
being entirely Spring Framework for the
完全是Spring Framework
dough based in spring from a furrow
春季起皱的面团
really enabling the things that boot can
真正启用引导可以
do and our spring XP initiative going
这样做，我们的春季XP计划将继续进行
into big data scenarios data ingestion a
大数据场景中的数据摄取
fresh new approach to think about those
考虑这些的全新方法
kinds of architectures all of those
所有这些类型的架构
things are spring from a coral based or
东西是来自珊瑚的春天
will be spring from crow based in the
来自乌鸦的春天
very very new future here so we're going
非常非常新的未来，所以我们要去
to focus on Spring Framework for the
专注于Spring Framework
remainder of the presentation but
演示文稿的其余部分，但
definitely check out a few of the other
肯定检查其他一些
projects that we're doing here spring
春天我们在这里做的项目
dudes in particular I'm going to to talk
帅哥，我要特别谈
about it just a little bit to refer to
关于它只是一点点参考
it if you a few more times so this
如果你再几次的话
presentation is about the spring
演讲是关于春天的
framework perspective itself more
框架视角本身
traditionally framework oriented but
传统上面向框架，但
keep in mind there were fresh new ways
请记住，有新鲜的新方法
to actually use spring the framework in
实际使用Spring Framework
spring in terms of middleware
中间件方面的春天
functionality with other projects in a
与其他项目中的功能
portfolio
作品集
so let's start with a a recap of the
因此，我们先来回顾一下
state of the art the
最先进的
theories I just like you two to go with
我只喜欢你们两个理论
me through a few slides indicating code
通过几张指示代码的幻灯片来指导我
examples showing code examples that
显示代码示例的示例
indicates a few important features in
表示中的一些重要功能
the spring framework three generation
Spring Framework 三代
it's basically the heart of the
这基本上是
component model of the annotation based
基于注释的组件模型
component bar what does it look like in
组件栏看起来像什么
in the spring framework three generation
在 Spring Framework 三代
and let's start with a component here
让我们从这里的组件开始
that's just a regular Java class
那只是一个普通的Java类
annotated with few annotations making it
带有少量注释的注释
a first-class citizen in the spring
春天的头等公民
component model and we we actually see
组件模型，我们实际上看到了
three kinds of annotations here we have
这里有三种注释
an X service annotation on top which is
在顶部的X服务注释是
a stereotype which basically tells us
刻板印象，基本上告诉我们
something about the class it tell it
关于班级的一些事情
formally tells us something about the
正式地告诉我们有关
class basically a formal way of saying
课堂基本上是一种正式的表达方式
this is a specific kind of class of
这是一类特殊的
service service class we have at Auto
汽车上的服务类别
Wyatt which is a good example for a
怀亚特（Wyatt）是一个很好的例子
dependency injection annotation you
依赖注入注解你
could also use JSF 3:38 inject here or
也可以在此处使用JSF 3:38注入，或
you could use Springs at value or in
您可以在有价值的地方使用Springs
similar places with expressions those
那些表达类似的地方
are all dependency injection and
都是依赖注入和
notations they basically identify a
符号基本上可以识别
constructor here as the primary target
此处的构造函数作为主要目标
of injection if no other indications are
如果没有其他适应症，则应注射
given if there's no other other metadata
如果没有其他元数据，则给出
influencing this the container will will
影响这一点的容器将
choose this one in a simple scenario
在一个简单的场景中选择这个
it's also why it can also be used on
这也是为什么它也可以用于
fields and methods of course the third
当然是第三种领域和方法
category down there is a transactional
类别下有交易
an example for a declarative service
声明式服务的示例
annotation there would be of course
注解当然会有
others in other domains as scheduled for
预定在其他域中的其他人
example for a crunch-ry' essential force
紧缩必不可少的例子
they all allow you to tap into
它们都允许您利用
middleware services
中间件服务
through the use of component-level
通过使用组件级
annotations but that's that's run time
批注，但这就是运行时间
impact right there's always runtime
影响总是存在运行时
impact spring as a as a as a component
冲击弹簧作为一个组件
container can discover components in the
容器可以发现
class pass through searching for
全班通过寻找
stereotypes for compliance stereotypes
遵守定型观念的成见
so at Service Above can actually serve
所以在服务之上可以实际服务
as kind of an an identification mark in
作为一种识别标记
the class pass for class cough searches
全班通行证
at also Wyatt
在怀亚特
of course has random impact it makes the
当然会有随机的影响
spring choose this constructor or one of
春天选择此构造函数或其中之一
the annotated constructors when when
带注释的构造函数何时
creating a new instance of that sales
创建该销售的新实例
class a transaction that has obvious
对具有明显特征的交易进行分类
round time impact right yeah
整场比赛对吧
container will will begin the
容器将开始
transaction before it invokes your
交易在调用您的
method implementation and it will commit
方法实现，它将提交
it or roll it back at the very end
或在最后回滚
that's the runtime impact of those
那是那些对运行时间的影响
things but that's let's take a step back
事情，但这让我们退后一步
we look at the piece of source code here
我们在这里看一段源代码
and those annotations are as much about
这些注释与
the readability of that source code as
该源代码的可读性为
they are about runtime impact so forget
它们与运行时的影响有关，因此请忘记
about the random impact for a moment you
关于暂时的影响
see a Java class here the F service and
在F服务中看到Java类
notation tells us something about the
记号告诉我们有关
role of that class in actually a
那个班级实际上在
descriptive nicely voided way each
每个描述性的无效方式
transactional has or something about the
交易性的东西或关于
methods the method is transactional it
方法是事务性的
basically formally defines
基本上正式定义
characteristics of that methods that are
该方法的特点是
also important to the reader of that
对读者来说也很重要
class even at all to Wyatt in terms of
甚至根本就不及悦
winning this constructor is or to Wyatt
赢得这个建设者是或怀亚特
if no other information is given so they
如果没有提供其他信息，那么他们
those are really descriptive metadata
那些真的是描述性的元数据
elements in your source code that's what
您的源代码中的元素就是
the annotations are initially and from a
注释最初是来自
design perspective that's what they
他们就是设计观点
primarily should be ram typing a runtime
主要应该是ram输入运行时
impact follows from there
随之而来的影响
so that's a component class a typical
这是典型的组件类
component class many of the imitations
组件类的许多模仿
in spring are composable as of spring
春季时可合成
through that one if Reta two in
通过那一个如果雷塔两个
particular composable means you can
特殊的可组合方式意味着您可以
build your own limitations and use
建立自己的限制和使用
spring for standard annotations the
用于标准注释的弹簧
out-of-the-box annotations as meta
现成的注释作为元
annotations this may be a little unusual
注释，这可能有点不寻常
initially but fundamentally it's a
最初但从根本上讲
completely normal thing to do you build
完全正常的事情要做
a new type in your code base it's not an
您的代码库中的新类型不是
interface it's not a class it's an ad
界面，不是课程，而是广告
interface it's an annotation type and in
界面，它是一种注释类型
order to define the type you add
为了定义您添加的类型
annotations on top of that type
该类型顶部的注释
so my service annotation shown here is a
所以这里显示的我的服务注释是
custom annotation of yours as an example
以您的自定义注释为例
basically combining the characteristics
基本结合特点
of a standard spring ed service
标准弹簧维修服务
defaulting the scope to session marking
将范围默认为会话标记
it as primary which means if the type
它是主要的，这意味着如果类型
match is not unique this one is
比赛不是唯一的，这是
preferably injected into other
最好注入其他
components and a default transaction
组件和默认交易
rule even these rules basically are
即使这些规则基本上是
combined into one single at my service
为我服务合二为一
in addition from that perspective it's a
从这个角度来看，这是一个
kind of short cutting model every time
每次都有一种捷径模型
you say at my service
你说我的服务
what you're actually saying is it
你实际上是在说
service at obsession a primary sempia
痴迷于初级感觉
transactional roller bus
事务性滚筒客车
however the short cutting is kind of a
但是捷径有点像
really nice benefit it's as much about
真正的好处是
the name as it is about the short
短名称
cutting my service might not be the
削减我的服务可能不是
greatest name in the world but the name
世界上最伟大的名字，但名字
is basically up to you you're free to
基本上取决于您，您可以自由选择
choose your own name and I would
选择你自己的名字，我会
definitely recommend using a good
绝对建议使用一个好的
meaningful expressive name within your
您内的有意义的表达性名称
your layout within your application
您的应用程序中的布局
architecture maybe maybe all the service
建筑也许所有的服务
account service or a specific kind of
帐户服务或特定类型的
service role has a meaning in your
服务角色对您有意义
architecture by all means if you're
如果您是
building custom annotations choose good
建立自定义注释选择好
names that actually correlate to to
实际与之相关的名称
basically terms in your architecture
基本上是您架构中的术语
at my service of course hero any other
我当然要为英雄服务
such annotation can be used on any
这样的注释可以在任何
number of types so to benefit from the
类型的数量，以便从中受益
short cutting nature of these things you
这些东西的捷径是你
can use them on hundreds of types as
可以在数百种类型上使用它们
necessary and they always express the
必要的，他们总是表达
combination of characteristics above
以上特征的组合
this is a stereotype a notation being
这是一种刻板印象
composed many other kinds of annotations
组成了许多其他类型的注释
in spring can be composed in the same
在春天可以组成在同一
way you can build custom scope
建立自定义范围的方式
annotations you can build custom
您可以构建自定义的注释
transaction annotations even custom be
交易注释甚至可以自定义
definition annotations or a custom
定义注释或自定义
injection annotation right the
注入注释正确
composition model here works basically
构图模型在这里基本起作用
for almost any kind of annotation in in
适用于几乎所有类型的注释
the spring framework
Spring Framework
an important part of our configuration
我们配置的重要组成部分
model in the spring 3 generation that's
春季3代的模型
the configuration configuration classes
配置配置类
configuration classes are fundamentally
配置类基本上是
a collection of factory methods that in
工厂方法的集合
combination with specific annotations
与特定注释结合
serve as the finishing points for spring
充当春天的终点
beans so basically you can define any
豆，所以基本上您可以定义任何
number of spring beans through
通过的Spring bean 数量
configuration classes instead of putting
配置类，而不是放置
them into XML bean definitions by name
按名称将它们转换为XML bean定义
and type and in a few external
和类型，并在一些外部
properties being set
设置的属性
we're basically switching the focus and
我们基本上是在改变重点，
we're saying alright the heart of it all
我们说的一切都很好
is the factory method that builds the
是构建方法的工厂方法
instance that's like this my book admin
像这样的实例我的书管理员
service messaging the name of the
服务消息传递的名称
factory method is the default bean name
工厂方法是默认的bean名称
the return type serves as the kind of
返回类型用作
initial bean type is what we build in
最初的bean类型是我们构建的
instance the add bean annotation
实例添加bean注释
basically marks it as producing a bean
基本上将其标记为生产咖啡豆
definition you can also specify
您还可以指定定义
additional characteristics at that level
该级别的其他特征
can add a lazy notation a primary
可以添加一个主要的惰性符号
notation qualifies that sort of thing at
记号在
this level the configuration class can
此级别的配置类可以
have any number of such acting methods
有很多这样的表演方法
they can call each other with special
他们可以互相打个招呼
semantics where the springs lifecycle
生命周期中的语义
management still very much applies even
管理仍然非常适用
for calls within its being methods
用于存在方式内的调用
there's a stereotype on top at
在上面有一个刻板印象
configuration basically says we're
配置基本上说我们
within a special kind of class we're
在特殊的课堂上
within a configuration class spring
在配置类spring中
stereotype mode in action for this out
刻板印象模式为此而行动
of the box configuration class mode
框配置类模式的
layer
层
the there can be any number of
可以有任意数量的
configuration classes in your system you
您系统中的配置类
can have one with hundreds with 100
可以有一百个有一百个
ethnic methods or a hundred
民族方法或一百
configuration classes with one add
一加的配置类
method each it's up to you so they are
方法取决于你，所以他们
also a unit of combining a certain being
也是结合某某的单位
a range meant so you can basically use
范围意味着您基本上可以使用
them as a kind of structural element for
它们作为一种结构元素
structuring your your configuration
结构化您的配置
arrangement in a in a comprehensive form
全面安排
you know also in a uniform that just
你也知道穿制服
allows you to to follow what you
让您跟随自己
actually meant to consider there is to
实际上意味着要考虑
further kinds of annotations shown here
此处显示的其他注释
and just quickly a note on them there's
很快便有关于他们的注释
an ad profile on top its profile is a
在其个人资料上方的广告个人资料是
simple kind of of condition of being
一种简单的存在状态
definition condition that basically says
基本上说的定义条件
the beans defined by this configuration
此配置定义的bean
class I only actually being registered
我只实际注册的课程
with the container if the profile called
如果配置文件调用容器
standalone is marked as active on
独立服务器标记为在
startup then and only then there can be
然后启动，只有那时
any number of profiles so you can have a
任何数量的个人资料，因此您可以
like whole arrangement the whole matrix
就像整个矩阵一样
of profile if you want to combining
如果要合并的个人资料
different variants of setting up your
设置您的不同变体
justice from your application through
从您的申请到通过
like a combination of profiles there can
像是个人资料的组合
be profiles that refer to specific
是指特定的配置文件
verticals in your in your architecture
您的架构中的垂直行业
or you can have profiles for specific
或者您可以具有特定的配置文件
random random platforms or for specific
随机随机平台或针对特定
target middleware that your that you are
目标中间件，即您是您
configured to interact with so profiles
配置为与个人资料交互
are really a very flexible mechanism but
是一个非常灵活的机制，但是
they are fundamentally pretty static
他们基本上是静态的
profiles have a name those profile names
配置文件的名称是那些配置文件名称
may be set as active on startup that's
可能被设置为在启动时处于活动状态
basically it we're going to revisit this
基本上，我们将重新讨论这一点
from a spring framework for perspective
从 Spring Framework 的角度来看
in a few months another just a quick
再过几个月又很快
focus within this
专注于此
component model type matches play a play
零部件模型类型匹配播放播放
an important role you can refer to a
您可以参考的重要角色
specific in my name if you want to have
具体要用我的名字
it injected traditionally with external
传统上是用外部注射
beam definition formats that's what you
光束定义格式就是您所需要的
would do that's also what you would do
会做那也是你会做的
with the address or sanitation in the
地址或环境卫生
annotation based component model however
但是基于注释的组件模型
we add auto wire and they inject too
我们添加了自动电线，他们也注入了
basically indicating a type match here
基本上在这里表示类型匹配
you're saying I've got a constructor or
你是说我有一个构造函数或
a field or whatever here the constructor
字段或其他构造函数
has an argument it takes an account
有一个论点需要考虑
repository may have any number of
存储库可以具有任意数量的
arguments but in this example it's just
参数，但在此示例中，
one an account repository
一个帐户存储库
it basically requests a dependency of
它基本上要求依赖
type account repository by type
按类型输入帐户存储库
teehee
嘻嘻
the idea is that in 80% of the cases
这个想法是在80％的情况下
there's only one match for the given
给定只有一场比赛
type registered with the container to
在容器中注册的类型
begin with keep in mind type matches in
首先要记住类型匹配
spring
弹簧
refer to the well-defined set of beam
参考定义明确的光束
definitions currently managed in the
当前在
container so it's about actually
容器，所以实际上
registers being definitions
寄存器是定义
it's not about arbitrary beams that hang
这不是关于悬挂的任意光束
around in your class path and happen to
在你上课的路上，碰巧
match the type
匹配类型
it's about registered component classes
关于注册的组件类
with that are registered with the
与该注册
container for example the profile
容器，例如配置文件
mechanism shown before can actually pre
之前显示的机制实际上可以预
select what's actually registered with
选择实际注册的内容
the container can serve as a kind of
该容器可以用作一种
filtering mechanism for some things not
某些事情没有过滤机制
to go in in some scenarios however in
在某些情况下进入
any in any given kind of arrangement
任何形式的安排
you've got a number of things define
你有很多定义
some injection points are shown above
上面显示了一些注入点
this one once in the country posit or
这一次在该国
some definition points typically in a
一些定义点通常在
completely different corner of the
完全不同的角落
system some configuration classes
系统一些配置类
probably there's a beam defining there's
可能有一条光束定义了
a be a factory method defining a beam of
是定义光束的工厂方法
type the contrapositive spring is
键入相反的弹簧是
basically about making that connection
基本上是关于建立连接
when when the injection point says i
当注射点说我
want in a concrete posit or e spring
想要在一个具体的位置或春天
looks at the set of beams find matches
看着光束的集合找到匹配项
by type or account repository if there's
按类型或帐户存储库（如果有）
only one all is good if there are
如果有的话，只有一件是好的
several matches we have to we have to
我们必须要进行的几场比赛
rely on additional metadata you have to
依靠额外的元数据
help us basically and what we see here
基本上帮助我们，我们在这里看到的
the qualifiers I serve exactly the
我所服务的预选赛
purpose you would only use qualifiers if
目的是您仅在以下情况下使用限定词
the type match is not unique so account
类型匹配不是唯一的，因此帐户
repository let's assume there is more
假设有更多存储库
than one match maybe a production match
一场比赛或一场生产比赛
in the testing match both are registered
在测试比赛中都注册了
with the container at the same time then
与容器同时
you can add the add qualifier notation
您可以添加添加限定符表示法
in this case with a spring qualifier
在这种情况下，使用弹簧预选赛
production to your injection point above
生产到您上面的注射点
you can add the same qualifier to the
您可以将相同的限定词添加到
definition point below so the factory
下面的定义点，所以工厂
method
方法
spring would immediately without any
春天将立即没有任何
further setup consume that additional
进一步的设置会消耗掉额外的
information when connecting the pieces
连接件时的信息
here so it would say ok account
在这里，所以它会说好的帐户
repository it is
它是存储库
well we have a qualified production
好，我们有合格的产品
there is an account repository match it
有一个与之匹配的帐户存储库
also has a qualified production so those
也有合格的产品，所以那些
obviously go together let's inject
显然一起去注入
exactly that one so that's that's
正是那个，那就是
qualifies to be used when type matches
符合类型匹配时使用的条件
are not unique we're going to revisit
不是唯一的，我们要重新审视
this as well from a spring fall
春天来了
perspective
透视
last but not least in this quick
最后但并非最不重要的一点
state-of-the-art tour NBC controllers
最先进的NBC巡回演出控制器
and on I'm not going to talk much about
而且我不会谈论太多
the NBC controls themselves I suppose
我想NBC会控制自己
most of you are familiar with them let's
你们大多数人都熟悉他们
look at them from a design perspective
从设计的角度来看他们
they have a stereotype above at
他们在上面有一个刻板印象
controller it has a number of methods
控制器它有很多方法
method level mapping annotations NBC
方法级映射注释NBC
controllers are basically an endpoint
控制器基本上是一个端点
model they define HTTP based endpoints
他们定义基于HTTP端点的模型
with incoming HTTP requests being mapped
传入的HTTP请求被映射
onto endpoint methods
端点方法
3d requests piping annotations hereby
3D特此请求管道注释
paths we use additionally use the
我们使用的路径另外使用
parameter signature here so the
参数签名在这里，所以
parameter signature may be pretty
参数签名可能很漂亮
important for each such method our finds
对于我们发现的每种此类方法都很重要
book method has a long ID which in
book方法的ID很长，
itself doesn't really mean much
本身并不意味着什么
remember source code readability if you
如果您记得源代码的可读性
look at just a long idea what is this
看一个长的主意，这是什么
right there are no magic rule attached
对，没有魔力法则
to it quite so easily we use parameter
如此容易，我们使用参数
level annotations typically to indicate
级别注释通常用于指示
what kind of parameter this is so in our
这在我们中是什么样的参数
case here we say long ID that's an ADD
在这里，我们说长ID是ADD
path variable it's a parameter level
路径变量，它是参数级别
annotation if there are several
注释是否有几个
parameters for our methods each of the
每个方法的参数
parameters may have its own annotations
参数可能有自己的注释
or typically a single annotation per
或通常每个
parameter in this case we say it's a
在这种情况下，我们说它是一个
path variable
路径变量
this parameter refers to this method
此参数引用此方法
parameter here refers to the path
这里的参数指的是路径
variable in the part of the bus
公交车部分可变
there's an ID variable defined in the
在其中定义了一个ID变量
path mapping that's what we refer to it
路径映射就是我们所说的
can be several of those path variables
可以是这些路径变量中的几个
so we rely on the parameter name to
所以我们依靠参数名称来
point to a specific variable by a name
通过名称指向特定变量
and we automatically convert it to long
我们会自动将其转换为long
because we can infer it from the
因为我们可以从
signature so this is this is about
签名，这是关于
source code readability the source code
源代码的可读性源代码
should basically say what it does in
基本上应该说出它在做什么
pretty obvious ways even to people who
甚至对于那些
are not so familiar with intricate
对复杂的事物不那么熟悉
detail and the random behaviors of
的细节和随机行为
course derived from the same annotation
源自相同注解的课程
annotations spring this spring's
注释春天，今年春天
dispatcher servlet there's a good job at
调度程序servlet擅长于
that basically intro specs get requested
基本上要求介绍规格
communications all the parameter
通讯所有参数
annotations and just
注释和公正
that's the right thing according to a
根据一个说法，这是正确的事情
set of rules one specific note here the
一组规则这里有一个具体说明
ID parameter we already explored that
我们已经探讨过的ID参数
it's name is relevant there may be
它的名称是相关的，可能有
several path variables they match by
他们匹配的几个路径变量
name
名称
however in standard Java there is no
但是在标准Java中没有
representation of the parameter name in
参数名称的表示形式
the bytecode basically for method
方法的字节码
parameters and constructor parameters
参数和构造函数参数
the the name of those parameters sits in
这些参数的名称位于
the source code in your java files but
Java文件中的源代码，但是
it's not preserved when we compile it
编译时不保留
down to bytecode in the bytecode it's
向下到字节码中的字节码
just an index in the type that's what
只是类型的索引
parameters have no name in JDK six and
参数在JDK 6中没有名称，并且
seven what we do on in on Springfree on
七，我们在Springfree上的工作
spring 3 and also in spring for when we
春季3以及春季
run on to DQ 6 and 7 is if there's no
继续执行DQ 6和7，如果没有
further information given we need to
鉴于我们需要的更多信息
know that name so if you don't
知道那个名字，所以如果你不知道
explicitly save out the name of the path
明确保存路径名称
variable if you can do that at path
如果您可以在路径上执行此操作
variable and an attribute ID you can you
您可以使用变量和属性ID
can help us that way but then you're
可以这样帮助我们，但是你
repeating yourself we don't want you to
重复自己，我们不希望你
repeat yourself so this what we see here
再说一遍，所以这就是我们在这里看到的
is actually preferred but then we need
实际上是首选，但是我们需要
to learn about the name at runtime that
在运行时了解名称
works as long as you compile your
只要您编译
classes with the dash debug compiler
破折号调试编译器的类
flag then the compiler basically insert
标志然后编译器基本上插入
to debug section in a debug symbol
在调试符号中调试部分
section into your class file which
部分到您的类文件中
happens to contain the parameters for
碰巧包含用于的参数
all methods and constructors that have a
所有具有
body so not very strict and interface
身体所以不是很严格和界面
methods but four methods in
方法，但有四种方法
implementation tasks that's all we need
我们所需的实施任务
here we basically read debug symbols we
在这里，我们基本上阅读了调试符号
use ASM parse the class files with the
使用ASM与
debug single section we cache it of
调试单个部分，我们将其缓存
course and then we can infer the
当然，然后我们可以推断
parameter name from there that's the
从那里的参数名称
best we can do on JDK 6 instead we're
我们可以在JDK 6上做到最好
going to revisit this as a zip revisit
将以zip方式重新访问
this as you may have guessed
您可能已经猜到了
all right spring from a photo though is
从照片上可以看到的春天是
basically an attempt to raise the
基本上是试图提高
baseline and we're going to just explain
基线，我们将只解释一下
what this really means in in a moment
片刻之后这实际上意味着什么
but it's also fundamentally improving on
但它也从根本上改善了
the spring karmic three component model
春季业力三要素模型
and taking it to the next level actually
并将其实际提升到一个新的水平
in many subtle details from from the
从许多细微的细节
component bottle perspective a lot of it
成分瓶的观点很多
is about revisited runtime and behavior
关于重新访问运行时和行为
the program the component model is very
该程序的组件模型非常
much what you used to work with in
您曾经在其中工作过的很多东西
Spring Framework 3 here so if existing
Spring Framework 3在这里，如果存在的话
Spring Framework 3 occasions and
Spring Framework 3次
existing Spring Framework three know-how
现有的Spring Framework 的三大诀窍
can just move along and then spring from
可以前进，然后从
before we're building on it refining it
在我们对其进行完善之前
fine-tuning it
对其进行微调
and we're upgrading it to a July 8th
我们将其升级到7月8日
level all right before I start let's
在开始之前先水平
define the baseline what do we mean here
定义基线我们在这里是什么意思
fundamentally spring filmic four as a
从根本上讲电影四
generation of the framework is defined
定义了框架的生成
to serve the needs of 2014 and beyond
满足2014年及以后的需求
here it's basically a very
这基本上是一个非常
forward-looking perspective that we're
我们的前瞻性观点
applying here we take application
在这里申请我们接受申请
architectures as they are being used
正在使用的架构
right now as they are being developed
现在正在开发中
right now which are not necessarily your
现在不一定是你的
traditional application server based
基于传统的应用服务器
architectures
建筑
it's about embedded web service
这是关于嵌入式Web服务的
bootstrapping an application with an
用一个自举程序
embedded web server it's about talking
嵌入式Web服务器是关于交谈
to non-relational data stores or other
非关系数据存储或其他
kinds of non traditional data stores
各种非传统数据存储
it's about lightweight messaging far
关于轻量级消息传递
from the rather heavy enterprise
来自相当沉重的企业
integration style of messaging that's
消息传递的集成风格
that's been so common it's about
那已经很普遍了
WebSockets file communication
WebSockets文件通讯
architectures between clients and
客户与
servers or different parts of a server
服务器或服务器的不同部分
system and it's in general about
系统，它通常是关于
asynchronous processing basically about
异步处理基本上关于
composing your application in a way that
编写应用程序的方式
allows you to make the best possible use
让您尽最大可能
of the processing power that you have
您拥有的处理能力
available at runtime but if you have a
在运行时可用，但如果您有
multi-core machine you better define
您最好定义的多核计算机
your system to it so make some good use
您的系统，所以要好好利用
of those cores and it's not always so
这些核心，但并非总是如此
easy peazy of a web applications tend
Web应用程序容易泛滥成灾
for other kinds of applications I
对于其他类型的应用
suppose but there are many kinds of
应该，但是有很多种
applications where there's many kinds of
有很多种类的应用
systems where this becomes a real
真正成为现实的系统
challenge the idea here is from a
挑战这里的想法来自
programming model perspective that we're
我们在编程模型方面的观点
not doing anything truly magic we're not
没有做任何真正不可思议的事情，我们不是
trying to take your code and to
试图把你的代码，并
interpret it in a fancy way on on the
以一种奇妙的方式解释它
multi-core architecture we allow you to
多核架构，我们允许您
define an application architecture of
定义一个应用程序架构
your choice and the framework basically
您的选择和框架基本上
supports you in your in your challenge
支持您应对挑战
along your way of building a system for
在构建系统的过程中
those for those kinds of scenarios so
那些情况下的
typically you you pretty explicit use
通常，您相当明确地使用
besides you declare when you want to go
除了声明何时要去
asynchronous you explicitly build
您显式构建的异步
messaging endpoints spring assists you
消息传递端点春季帮助您
to do that in a clean convenient are
在干净方便的地方做到这一点
inconsistent way
不一致的方式
we interpret the baseline term also as a
我们将基准术语也解释为
as a dependency baseline so as of spring
作为依存基准，从春季开始
from a folder though it's JDK 6 plus
从文件夹（虽然是JDK 6 plus）
Java SE 6 plus actually it's even it's
Java SE 6 plus实际上甚至是
even a little bit more than that we
甚至比我们多一点
require JDK 6 update 18 as an API level
需要JDK 6 update 18作为API级别
or later of course that's like an early
或以后，当然就像
2010 baseline that's JDK 6 upgraded to
将JDK 6的2010年基准升级到
include exp 1.4 and specs 1 to 2 for
包括exp 1.4和规范1至2
example in the IBM world that happened
IBM世界中发生的例子
at around the same time so we need dead
大约在同一时间，所以我们需要死
API level from early 2010 as a minimum
至少从2010年初开始的API级别
dependency of course JDK 7 plays a
当然，JDK 7的依赖关系
central role here it would be the
在这里的中心作用是
mainstream JDK that spring framework for
主流的JDK那个Spring Framework
is expected to be used with initially we
预计最初将与我们一起使用
also raise the baseline to Java EE 6
也将基线提高到Java EE 6
plus as a guideline right it's about
另外，作为指导原则，它是关于
it's about individual specifications
关于个别规格
here not about v6 as a platform level we
这里不是关于v6作为平台级别的
are we require JPA to the donor for
我们是否要求JPA给捐助者
example
例
we also focus on server 3 though both of
我们还专注于服务器3，尽管两者
them being central parts of physics
它们是物理学的核心部分
however server 3 though we technically
但是服务器3虽然我们在技术上
only require for development in mind so
只需要考虑发展，所以
if you want to use our mocks or that
如果您想使用我们的模拟游戏
sort of stuff our set of it of several
一些东西，我们的几个
dpi marks then you'll have to be on
dpi标记，那么您必须先打开
server 3 out there however at deployment
服务器3在那里部署
time we are served it to the 5
时间我们送达5
compatible as long as you're not using
兼容，只要您不使用
actual server 3 or functionality which
实际的服务器3或功能
fortunately is easy to identify so as
幸运的是很容易识别
long as you're not using web application
只要您不使用Web应用程序
initialized or async processing you're
您正在初始化或异步处理
you're pretty much all set even if your
即使您的
target environment is a circuit to this
目标环境是为此的回路
5 container
5个容器
it's very explicitly defined to be that
非常明确地定义为
way because we understand that there's
方式，因为我们了解
plenty of existing runtime environments
大量现有的运行时环境
with a server to the size containers out
用服务器将大小容器取出来
there on Java 6 possible to use JP 800
Java 6上可以使用JP 800
butts over to the safest that's what we
碰到最安全的就是我们
still want to be compatible with we took
仍然想与我们兼容
the opportunity to remove all deprecated
删除所有已弃用的机会
packages most of them have been
包大多数
duplicated for a long long time so it
复制了很长时间很久
shouldn't come as a surprise we remove
我们删除不应令人惊讶
many deprecated methods as well some of
许多不推荐使用的方法以及
them remain in case anyone is checking
它们保留，以防有人检查
some of them remain because we're
其中一些仍然存在，因为我们
pragmatic about it we understand that
务实的我们了解到
there are pre-compiled third-party
有预编译的第三方
libraries out there talking to some
图书馆在和一些人聊天
methods that have been deprecated along
不推荐使用的方法
the way we preserve some of those
我们保留其中一些方式
methods if if we know that there are
如果我们知道有
commonly used pre-compiled libraries out
常用的预编译库
there
那里
they cannot so easily change we had to
他们不能轻易改变，我们不得不
make a few compromises in some cases we
在某些情况下，我们会做出一些妥协
upgrade other projects in our portfolio
升级我们投资组合中的其他项目
to be compatible with spring from a pro
与专业人士的弹簧兼容
but in most cases you can use existing
但在大多数情况下，您可以使用现有的
versions as you're used to so even
您习惯的版本
existing spring security versions for
现有的Spring安全版本
example would still work with spring
这个例子仍然适用于春季
from a folder though don't have to be
从文件夹，虽然不必
upgraded immediately
立即升级
a central focus of course of the spring
春季当然是重点
framework for generation is our Java age
生成框架是我们的Java时代
story we raise the baseline to JDK six
故事我们将基准提高到JDK六
plus we we have JDK 7 as a mainstream
另外，我们以JDK 7为主流
level of the JDK however the most
JDK级别，但是最多
interesting part are from the JDK
有趣的部分来自JDK
perspective is certainly Java 8 and
观点当然是Java 8和
Spring Framework force ways of being a
Spring Framework迫使人们成为一种
good citizen in Java 8 world
Java 8世界的好公民
it's about Java 8 language features it's
关于Java 8语言功能
about Java 8 API features and it's about
关于Java 8 API功能，它与
runtime compatibility with JDK 8 so kind
与JDK 8的运行时兼容性是如此
of independent in some way with the
在某种程度上独立于
language features which is of course a
语言功能当然是
data probably most interesting card we
数据可能是我们最有趣的卡片
have named that expressions as just a
将该表达式命名为
really nice addition to to the Java
对Java来说真的很不错
language I expect this to be very
我希望这是非常语言
commonly used in the in the near future
在不久的将来常用
that it's really great for many use
真的很好用
cases and it's also a great fit for
案例，也非常适合
Springs API 5 as we're going to see in a
Springs API 5，我们将在
few moments method references are kind
片刻的方法引用很亲切
of a variant of lambda expressions for
的lambda表达式的变体
lambda expressions are being compiled to
lambda表达式被编译为
for the purposes of this presentation we
在此演示中，我们
are only going to focus on a few
只专注于一些
selected features in the Javaid space
Javaid空间中的选定功能
here if you'd like to learn more about
如果您想了解更多信息，请点击这里
it we we are already doing Java 8
我们已经在做Java 8
oriented presentations we will be doing
我们将要进行的定向演示
each other it oriented webinar in the
彼此面向的网络研讨会
near future where we're going to dive a
在不久的将来，我们将潜水
little bit deeper but for the for
更深一点，但对于
today's purposes let's just focus on the
今天的目的让我们只专注于
most important benefits to to derive
最重要的好处
from this so I'm going to show you the
因此，我将向您展示
use of lambda expressions we're going to
使用lambda表达式
talk about JSF 3/10 dated time in a bit
再谈一下JSF 3/10的过时时间
more detail quickly mention repeatable
更多细节快速提及可重复
annotations what we can do with spring
注释我们可以用spring做些什么
annotations to support it and let me
注释来支持它，让我
also mention here parameter name
在此也提及参数名称
discovery we've been talking about
我们一直在谈论的发现
parameter names before the ability for a
能力之前的参数名称
frame looks to read parameter names for
框架看起来为读取参数名称
methods or constructors and in
方法或构造函数以及
application classes as of Java 8 this is
从Java 8开始的应用程序类
actually a first-class feature Java 8
实际上是一流的Java 8功能
comes
来了
- parameters compiler flag that allows
-参数编译器标志，允许
you to rather that instructs to tolerate
您宁愿指示宽容
compiler to include a parameter main
编译器包含参数main
section in in your class file and this
类文件中的部分
this section basically comes with
本节基本上带有
reflection API support so we can use
反射API支持，因此我们可以使用
standard API to read the parameter names
标准API读取参数名称
from such class you do need to specify
从此类中，您确实需要指定
that flag so it's not happening by
该标志，所以它不会发生
default but it's a first class feature
默认，但这是一流的功能
you don't have to switch to debug
您不必切换到调试
symbols you can just say - parameters
您可以说的符号-参数
that's it of course we also support the
就是这样，我们当然也支持
debug symbol very instantly you can also
您可以立即调试符号
compile the flashy bug would compile
编译华丽的错误会编译
with both it will work either way
两者都可以工作
but there's in any case there's
但无论如何都会有
first-class support for this feature in
对此功能的一流支持
Java 8 which is great because basically
Java 8很棒，因为基本上
makes us feel better about relying on
使我们对依靠感到更好
this in in our programming model in the
这在我们的编程模型中
cleanest version of our programming
我们程序最干净的版本
model we didn't technically rely on it
我们在技术上不依赖它的模型
we're ways to repeat yourself and avoid
我们是重复自己并避免的方法
that neat as mentioned but it's still
提到的整洁，但仍然
it's a great enabler where we don't have
这是我们没有的一个很好的推动者
to use ASM don't have to read class
使用ASM不必阅读课
files anymore whereas where the JDK
文件了，而JDK
itself enables us to do this as a first
本身使我们能够首先做到这一点
class feature right so we're going to
类功能正确，所以我们要
see a few examples in just a moment
马上看几个例子
but let me take the opportunity here to
但让我借此机会
point out another perspective on CDA
指出关于CDA的另一种观点
it's about runtime compatibility of
这是关于
existing applications when deployed to
现有应用程序部署到
Cherokee
切诺基
just imagine when not quite now alright
想象一下现在还不行的时候
but imagine in half a year's time in a
但想像在半年的时间里
year's time JDK 8 is going to show up in
一年的时间JDK 8将会出现在
deployment environments in some form in
某种形式的部署环境
some platforms as a service some cloud
一些平台即服务一些云
platforms and some data centers intern
平台和一些数据中心实习生
hosting options when deploying an
部署
existing application that's compiled for
为之编译的现有应用程序
TDC 6 or 7 - such a unique e8 based
TDC 6或7-基于独特的e8
deployment platform we're really not
部署平台，我们真的不是
relying on much there's no use of gyrate
依靠很多没有陀螺
language which is no use of one that
一种不使用的语言
they bytecode or anything like that it's
他们字节码或类似的东西
just about compatibility with reflection
与反射兼容
behavior
行为
and just general standard
只是一般的标准
implementations in the GDK libraries
GDK库中的实现
this is not entirely trivial but we did
这不完全是微不足道的，但是我们做到了
actually spend some time fine-tuning
实际花一些时间进行微调
spring as a framework to support that
春天作为支持这一点的框架
kind of scenario even even in the in the
即使在
little dark corners so taking an
小小的黑暗角落，因此
existing spring based application and
现有的基于Spring的应用程序和
deploying it to adjudicate platform
部署到裁定平台
maybe because you want to benefit from
也许是因为您想从中受益
from virtual machine enhancements in G
从G中的虚拟机增强功能
decade there are actually quite a few in
十年中实际上有很多
particular towards memory management
特别是内存管理
there may be a good enough reason to to
可能有足够的理由
deploy to dedicate for start without
部署专用于无
having to switch to to Java eight
不得不切换到Java 8
language features at all so those kinds
语言特点
of scenarios are officially supported as
的场景被正式支持为
well from our side with spring from a
从我们这边来的春天
food although primarily to some degree
食物虽然主要在某种程度上
also with the latest Spring Framework
还有最新的Spring Framework
through the two releases for existing
通过现有的两个版本
applications running on to the kid
在孩子身上运行的应用程序
all right let's have a look at language
好吧，让我们来看看语言
features lenders which is the central
特色贷款人是中央
language in Java it is actually a kind
Java语言实际上是一种
of closure but their lambda expressions
闭包，但它们的lambda表达式
they are a sweet short way to provide an
它们是提供一个
implementation of a callback interface
回调接口的实现
fundamentally the the whole idea behind
从根本上说，整个背后的想法
lambda expressions are that the compiler
lambda表达式是编译器
is a compiler feature so it's the
是编译器功能，因此
compiler actually processing them the
编译器实际上处理它们
compiler a introspect where the lambda
编译器内省lambda
expression is being applied it
表达式被应用了
automatically coerces it into an
自动将其强制转换为
implementation of a callback interface
回调接口的实现
so there has to be rules for those
所以必须有那些规则
clapping interfaces they have to
拍手，他们必须
basically be single method interfaces
基本上是单一方法接口
called functional interfaces in Java a
在Java中称为功能接口
terminology fortunately in in spring
春季幸运地使用了术语
api's you'll find many such called the
api，您会发现许多这样的
interfaces consider JDBC templates which
接口考虑JDBC模板
has like connection callback prepared
已准备好连接回调
statements that are Rome ever resulted
罗马曾经发表过的声明
extractor they are all natural natural
提取器都是天然的
functional interfaces Java 8 lambda
功能接口Java 8 lambda
expressions fundamentally by convention
基本上从惯例上表达
can be applied to those spring ApS very
可以非常适用于那些春季ApS
very naturally with actually without
很自然，实际上没有
changing the spring api's themselves
改变春天的api自己
those spring AP is in many cases dated
那些春季AP在很多情况下都过时了
back to like 2004 and 2005 at the same
回到2004年和2005年
time even ten years later there are
时间甚至十年后
natural citizens for the Java eight
爪哇八的自然公民
language conventions which is really
语言惯例
great to see from outside so spring as a
很高兴从外面看到春天
framework has to do quite a quite a few
框架必须做很多
things to enable the use of Java eight
启用Java八件事
language features in general the use of
语言功能的一般使用
the 1/8 bytecode level and so forth
1/8字节码级别，依此类推
however in terms of API design it's just
但是就API设计而言，
a natural fit so it's about JDBC
很自然，因此与JDBC有关
template GMS template has quite a few
模板GMS模板有很多
such called big interfaces we even have
这样的大接口，我们甚至有
a transaction template with the
具有以下内容的交易模板
transaction callback interface we have
我们拥有的事务回调接口
task executives tasks schedulers with
任务主管与任务计划程序
runnable and callable arguments passed
传递了可运行和可调用的参数
in again one method called big
再有一种叫做大的方法
interfaces so many many of those to be
接口太多了
found
发现
let's focus on two basic templates
让我们专注于两个基本模板
because we're going to show this in an
因为我们将在
example in just a moment
短短的例子
a typical JDBC template call may be
典型的JDBC模板调用可能是
let's just do it like this
让我们这样做
a typical GBC template call looks looks
一个典型的GBC模板调用看起来
like this the only unusual part here is
像这样，这里唯一不寻常的部分是
the use of lambda expressions but
使用lambda表达式，但是
fundamentally it's a regular typical
从根本上说，这是正常的
JDBC template query call the query
JDBC模板查询调用查询
method used here is the one that takes a
这里使用的方法是一种
string
串
the sequel string a prepared statement
续集字符串准备好的语句
setter
二传手
and the role mapper we see two calls
和角色映射器，我们看到了两个调用
basically identical calls with different
基本相同的通话，不同的
source layouts it's basically the same
源代码布局基本上是相同的
call repeated with different layer the
用不同的层重复调用
first line is the string argument for
第一行是字符串参数
the sequel statement the second one the
续集声明第二个
second argument after the comma is the
逗号后的第二个参数是
prepared statement set argument that's
准备好的语句集参数是
the unusual part we have a lambda
不寻常的部分，我们有一个lambda
expression here specified against an API
此处针对API指定的表达式
that expects a prepared statement setter
期望准备好的语句设置器
and the third argument is basically
第三个论点基本上是
matching against the Roma Bahn limited
与Roma Bahn Limited相匹配
spring so we have the string cast in a
春天，所以我们把琴弦浇在
prepared statement setter passed in
准备好的语句设置器传入
aroma / pasta they prepared steak and
他们准备牛排的香气/面食和
setter let's switch back for a moment
设置器，让我们切换一下
prepared statement said that has one
准备好的声明说有一个
callback method the name is irrelevant
回调方法名称无关
set values that anyway the prepared
设置无论如何准备的值
statement that comes in is important so
声明很重要，所以
it's a colleague interface that
这是一个同事界面
processes in an incoming prepared
准备进来的流程
statement can basically set any number
语句基本上可以设置任何数字
of parameters and that's exactly what
参数，而这正是
our lambda expression does here the PS
我们的lambda表达式在这里做PS
part before the error the PS part refers
PS部分指的是错误之前的部分
to that prepared statement arguments you
到准备好的语句参数
could also declare it with a type you
也可以用您声明的类型
could say prepared statement PS but you
可以说准备好的声明PS，但您
don't have to you can shorten it appears
不必，您可以缩短它的显示时间
and on the right hand side we have TD
在右侧，我们有TD
more or less domestic body in expression
表达上或多或少的家庭
style so it's not a full Java statement
样式，因此它不是完整的Java语句
it's in the kind of expression style
这是一种表达风格
Java statement where you perform a set
执行一组Java语句
string called PR set string single
称为PR的字符串设置单个字符串
statement on that incoming object on the
关于该传入对象的声明
prepared statement that's basically
基本上是准备好的陈述
preparedstatement setter method body so
准备语句设置器方法正文
you're going to in mentally you're
你会在精神上
probably going to have in your mind I
我可能会想到
could pass in an anonymous inner class
可以传递匿名的内部类
here new preparedstatement Sarah I'm
这是我准备的新的陈述莎拉
implementing the set values method
实现设定值方法
preparedstatement comes in within the
准备好的陈述出现在
method body I'm saying PS that string
方法主体，我说的是PS该字符串
and as a mental model that works just
作为一种心理模型
fine it's basically a kind of shortcut
好的，这基本上是一种捷径
instead of implementing anonymous inner
而不是实现匿名内部
classes with plenty of like mouth and
有很多像嘴巴和
method signatures around the actually
实际的方法签名
interesting code we focus on the really
有趣的代码，我们专注于
interesting code here we just specify
我们只在这里指定有趣的代码
the method body that's it we do the same
方法主体就是这样
for the role mapper in the next line the
下一行中的角色映射器
RS realm online Rome at but on our slide
RS Realm在线罗马位于，但在我们的幻灯片上
before has a resulted RS intro num
之前已产生RS介绍
coming in and it actually returns the
进来，它实际上返回
map object Metro returns a map object
地图对象Metro返回地图对象
for each role in the result set and
对于结果集中的每个角色，以及
that's exactly what our without a lambda
这就是我们没有lambda的情况
expression does here RS roll on come in
表达式在这里RS滚动进来
to two parameters here we refer to them
这里有两个参数
by name so we could say results at RS in
按名称，所以我们可以说RS中的结果
program but we don't have to the names
程序，但我们不必输入名称
are sufficient and on the right hand
足够并且在右边
side we have an lambda expression that
方面，我们有一个lambda表达式
says okay we basically build a new
说好吧，我们基本上建立了一个新的
person object we call our scattering one
人称对象，我们称其为散射
and RS get into that's maybe like name
和RS进入那可能就像名字
and age we pass them into person
和年龄，我们将它们传递给人
construct accepting them and we return
构建接受它们，我们返回
them so we don't see the return
他们，所以我们看不到回报
statement here but there's an implicit
声明在这里，但有一个隐含的
return statement here because metro
在这里返回声明，因为地铁
expects an object to be returned and
期望返回一个对象，
this expression evaluates to an object
此表达式求值为一个对象
so that's basically the shortest
所以基本上是最短的
possible version of a JDBC template call
JDBC模板调用的可能版本
with the use of two lambda expressions
使用两个lambda表达式
personally I find it particularly
我个人觉得特别
interesting to consider it examples with
有趣的考虑它的例子
multiple length expressions a single
多个长度表达式
lambda instead of an imminent anonymous
lambda而不是即将来临的匿名
in the class
在课堂里
it's nice enough for a start but if the
一开始就足够了，但是如果
power of lambda expressions really shows
Lambda表达式的力量真正表明
when you have calls that take several
当您接听一些电话时
callback interfaces as in our example
回调接口，如我们的示例
here
这里
our second example in the lower half of
下半部的第二个例子
the slide is the same basically as above
幻灯片基本上与上面相同
but with more traditional formatting
但采用更传统的格式
it's using a variant of lambda
它使用了lambda的变体
expressions that points to a regular
指向正则表达式
Java code block more like a regular Java
Java代码块更像常规Java
method body you could think so the peep
方法主体，您可能会这么认为
the PS are the previous step inside one
PS是其中的上一步
has a regular Java code block with
有一个常规的Java代码块
brackets a PS set string call inside
括号内的PS设置字符串调用
it ends with a semicolon there could be
它以分号结尾可能
several such segments inside it's a code
其中的几个这样的段是一个代码
block at the regular java code block it
在常规的Java代码处进行阻止
has to comply with standard java code
必须符合标准的Java代码
block rules that's why they the
阻止规则，这就是为什么
semicolon and so forth has to be there
分号等必须存在
the second lender the RS rona member
第二名贷款人RS rona成员
against the row member if again in the
针对行成员，如果再次出现在
second example it's a regular java code
第二个例子是常规的Java代码
block so it could have more than one
阻止，所以它可能不止一个
statement inside and since it's a
里面的声明，因为它是一个
regular java code block it has to have a
常规的Java代码块，它必须有一个
return statement as you can see here and
您在这里看到的return语句和
the semicolon at the end so that's
最后的分号是
really what lambda expressions can do to
Lambda表达式真的可以做什么
you and to your code they are basically
你和你的代码，他们基本上是
a way to provide an implementation of
提供实现的方式
the colleague interface the compiler
同事界面编译器
takes your lambda expression evaluated
评估您的lambda表达式
against the target point that you're
针对你的目标点
applying them to so it knows what they
应用它们，以便知道它们
go into right it sees a call against GBC
进入右侧，可以看到对GBC的呼叫
templates very method and it knows the
模板非常方法，它知道
signature of the target map and then it
目标地图的签名，然后
curves them into implementations of
将它们弯曲成的实现
those korvac interfaces at the runtime
这些korvac接口在运行时
lambdas actually gets compiled to method
lambdas实际上被编译为方法
references - like synthetic private
参考-像合成私人
methods in in the containing class it's
包含类中的方法是
actually a very efficient way of
实际上是一种非常有效的方法
representing them it's even slightly
代表他们甚至
more efficient than anonymous in the
比匿名更有效
classes would be but conceptually it
类将是但从概念上讲
really helps to think about them as kind
真的有助于他们善待自己
of an a shortcut way to implement an
一种实现
anonymous in the class even if that's
在课堂上是匿名的，即使那是
not exactly what happens at runtime
不完全是在运行时发生的情况
I find it conceptually useful
我发现它在概念上很有用
and if you look at the second example
如果你看第二个例子
below that really looks somewhat similar
下面看起来真的有点相似
to anonymous inner classes let's just
匿名内部类，让我们只是
know that's just no class technician no
知道那只是没有上课的技术人员
method signature by the regular method
常规方法的方法签名
buddy it's not so far from a from an
哥们，离一个不远
anonymous inner class arrangement
匿名内部阶级安排
however it fits on this slide right we
但是它适合这张幻灯片，我们
have two examples each with two lambda
有两个带有两个lambda的示例
expressions on a single slide here that
一张幻灯片上的表达式
really says it all tried it with
真的说一切都尝试过
anonymous inner classes it would be for
匿名内部类将用于
anonymous in the classes on the slide
在幻灯片上的课程中匿名
so that's lambdas and that's an almost
所以这是lambda，这几乎是
complete definition of lambdas that's
Lambda的完整定义是
basically what lambda expressions do
Lambda表达式基本上是做什么的
there's not much more to it we almost
我们几乎没有更多的东西了
explained I think we even covered all
解释说我认为我们甚至涵盖了所有
variants or regular variants of members
成员的变体或常规变体
it's not a particularly complex feature
这不是一个特别复杂的功能
if you spend half an hour or an hour
如果您花费半小时或一个小时
with them try to play with them in an
和他们一起尝试与他们一起玩
IDE for example in IntelliJ IDEA which
例如IntelliJ IDEA中的IDE
it's it's great debate support even at
即使在
this point you'll find them really
这一点你会发现他们真的
really useful and convenient and very
真的非常有用，方便而且非常
natural if you try them for an hour
如果你尝试一个小时自然
they're going to feel very natural
他们会觉得很自然
the rules are straightforward pretty
规则很简单
simple even if you'd like to understand
即使您想了解也很简单
what happens that at runtime it's
在运行时会发生什么
fundamentally a straightforward feature
根本上是一个简单的功能
the create addition to the to the java
Java的create补充
language since its convention based and
自约定以来的语言
can be used with existing api's and
可以与现有的api和
libraries as long as your runtime
库，只要您的运行时
environment is generally capable of
环境通常能够
working with Java eight based code
使用基于Java的八个代码
because you can only use this with
因为您只能将其与
source 1 or 8 level which implies target
源1或8级别，表示目标
1/8 level which implies 1.8 bytecode
1/8级，表示1.8个字节码
format in your class files so as long as
只要您的班级文件中的格式
your runtime frameworks are capable of
您的运行时框架能够
understanding and working with the 1/8
了解和使用1/8
bytecode level this is available to you
字节码级别可供您使用
right now remember JDK 8 is in release
现在记得JDK 8已发布
candidate mode as of this week the
截至本周的候选模式
recently released open JDK 8 build 124
最近发布的开放式JDK 8 build 124
is the release candidate build with
是发布候选版本
generally availability the general
一般可用性一般
availability date coming up in late
上市日期迟到
March so it's not far off if you'd like
三月，所以如果您愿意的话，距离不远
to start a new development project right
开始一个新的开发项目
now consider starting it or JDK 8 even
现在考虑启动它甚至JDK 8
at
在
this very point spring framework 4 is
这一点Spring Framework 4是
basically designed to support you right
基本上旨在为您提供支持
from this point in your development
从您开发的这一点开始
efforts that's why we have such early
努力，这就是为什么我们这么早
support for Java it may be you're not
支持Java可能不是
going to deploy until until later late
打算部署到晚些时候
2014 or even 2015 and you know it
2014年甚至2015年，你知道的
already because there's no reason not to
已经因为没有理由不
consider to deviate for such projects if
考虑如果这样的项目偏离
you know that it's going to be available
你知道它将可用
to you next year in production all right
明年生产给您
so much for the future of eight
对于八的未来来说太重要了
considerations quick to through other
快速考虑其他
GDK eight based features this is Joseph
GDK的八个基本功能是Joseph
310 date and time it's basically a kind
310日期和时间，基本上是一种
of successor to a child a time a fresh
一个孩子的继任者
reimplementation of the same concepts
重新实现相同的概念
which other time head it's not exactly
还有哪一次不完全是
identical if you look if you look into
如果你看的话就一样
the details it's in some cases it
在某些情况下它的细节
explicitly differs from to other time in
与明显不同
some arrangement and some some
一些安排和一些
conventions but initially at least it's
惯例，但起初至少是
yet they're quite similar the central
但它们与中央非常相似
part of Joseph 310 having new value
约瑟夫310的一部分具有新价值
types local date local date time and so
输入本地日期，本地日期时间等
forth physically expressive value types
第四种物理表达价值类型
to be used in your domain model or in
用于您的域模型或
your value types and replacing java.util
您的值类型并替换java.util
they'd fundamentally or java.util
他们从根本上还是java.util
calendar if you there was really the
日历，如果你真的有
only standard way to represent them
代表他们的唯一标准方法
before now you have standard expressive
在此之前，您具有标准的表现力
value types if it's just the date
值类型（如果只是日期）
without the time use local date if it's
如果没有时间，请使用本地日期
a look if it's a date enter time
看是否是日期输入时间
specification use local dead time it is
规范使用本地停滞时间
just the time within a day use local
只是一天之内的时间使用本地
time if it's a date and time defined for
时间，如果是为该日期和时间定义的
a very specific time zone use sound
一个非常特定的时区使用声音
date/time so for any such scenario
日期/时间，因此对于任何此类情况
there's a corresponding venue type
有相应的场地类型
that's the correct representation of
那是正确的表示
your value and your values implications
您的价值和价值含义
in your domain model it so it really
在您的域模型中
goes right into the heart of what we're
进入我们所关注的核心
doing
在做
building building domain models
建立建筑领域模型
representing data types from a spring
表示弹簧中的数据类型
perspective we support use a310 for our
观点，我们支持使用a310
format
格式
and binding framework in particular and
以及具有约束力的框架，特别是
for conversion to some degree but the
进行某种程度的转换，但
most important part is formatting and
最重要的部分是格式化和
binding consider Springs at day time
考虑在白天绑定Springs
format annotation which has been around
格式注释已经存在
since spring for you you could annotate
从春天开始，您可以注释
the field and say like this is a parsing
领域，并说像这样是解析
and rendering pattern for that value it
并为该值渲染模式
was primarily designed to be applied to
最初被设计用于
like travel you to date fields that
像旅行一样约会字段
otherwise wouldn't really say what they
否则不会真的说他们
are so that the pattern really was the
这样的模式才是真正的
only way to turn them into something
将它们变成东西的唯一方法
proper to know what you were passing
知道你在通过什么
from s of Joseph 3:10 here we still
从约瑟夫记3:10
support a datum for moment you can apply
暂时支持您可以申请的数据
a very specific custom parsing and
一个非常具体的自定义解析，
rendering pattern as a kind of default
呈现模式作为一种默认设置
Convention for Strings to be passed into
字符串传递公约
this field or for this field to be
该字段或该字段为
rendered out to some kind of text
呈现出某种文本
representation be it HTML or JSON based
基于HTML或JSON的表示形式
or whatever as long as it's textual a
或任何文字形式的
data informative if it were it
数据是否有用
however the server but interesting
但是服务器却很有趣
detail is that the value types are now
细节是值类型现在是
expressive enough for us to be able to
表现力足以使我们能够
more aggressively default here look at
更积极地默认这里看
the local date field above the birth
出生上方的本地日期字段
date field the a date-time format
date字段是一种日期时间格式
annotation is commented out because it's
注释被注释掉，因为它是
basically the default behavior if you
基本上是默认行为，如果您
don't specify any date/time form it here
不要在此处指定任何日期/时间形式
Springs binding and formatting framework
Springs绑定和格式化框架
looks at the value types and says like
看值类型说
local date it says it's the date so we
当地日期说是日期，所以我们
use the iOS L data representation update
使用iOS L数据表示法更新
time we just paid because local date set
我们刚刚支付的时间，因为设置了本地日期
so so we can more specifically default
所以我们可以更明确地默认
the conventions that we're using if no
如果没有，我们使用的约定
specific convention is given with Java
Java给出了特定的约定
util date that just wasn't possible so
util date，那是不可能的，所以
this is really great stuff in geni Kate
这真是Geni Kate的好东西
it's an API feature fundamentally but
从根本上说这是一个API功能，但是
it's an important API to agree on though
这是一个重要的API
the real benefit coming from Joseph
真正的好处来自约瑟夫
within here is going to show once all
在这里要显示一次
mainstream frameworks be them be like
主流框架就像它们
application frameworks web frameworks
应用程序框架Web框架
binding frameworks persistence
绑定框架持久性
frameworks once they all understand just
一旦他们都了解框架
a 310 by default the power is really
默认是310
going to show the power
展现力量
the state and time value types at the
的状态和时间值类型
same time we also support Joe design of
同时我们也支持Joe的设计
course we have been supporting two other
当然我们一直在支持另外两个
times in spring three oh and we still do
春天的三倍哦，我们仍然
in spring further though we require two
在春季，尽管我们需要两个
other time to the zone now so we even
现在其他时间到该区域，所以我们甚至
it's actually improved and extended to
它实际上已经改进并扩展到
other time support that comes with
附带的其他时间支持
spring form so if you're on JDK six and
春天的形式，所以如果您使用的是JDK 6和
seven in particular consider using
特别是七个考虑使用
childer time it will look very similar
幼稚的时间，它将看起来非常相似
to what you're seeing here just using
到您在这里看到的只是使用
Childre time inputs but the names of the
Childre时间输入，但输入的名称
many types in many cases identical and
许多类型在很多情况下都是相同的
spring accommodates for the API
弹簧容纳API
differences in many ways you can use a
您可以在许多方面使用差异
datum format so you can have a very
基准格式，因此您可以
similar experience with each other time
彼此相似的经历
on JDK six and seven but if you are on
在JDK 6和7上，但是如果您在
GD 8 then by all means consider the
GD 8然后一定要考虑
standard Java time types
标准Java时间类型
all right
好吧
quick note on repeatable annotations the
关于可重复注释的快速注释
above example is what you can do with
上面的例子是你可以做的
springtime ik 4 on Java 8 now add
现在在Java 8上添加spring ik 4
scheduled repeating it with two
预定重复两次
different conjugates on the same method
相同方法的不同共轭物
that wasn't possible with JDK 6 and 7 as
对于JDK 6和7，这是不可能的，因为
of JDK 8 for annotations that have been
JDK 8的注释
declared accordingly the above works the
据此宣布上述作品
compiler will accept it just fine we
编译器会接受就好了，我们
have to declare our our applicable
必须声明我们适用
annotations in a repeatable form now and
现在以可重复的形式注释
that's what we do as of spring from curl
那是我们从卷曲开始做的春天
so at schedule then the and a few others
所以按计划然后和其他几个
in spring basically annotations that
在春天基本上是注释
semantically can be repeated adequately
语义上可以充分重复
have to be repeated repeatable now in
现在必须重复可重复
the Java 8 compatible form if you're on
Java 8兼容表单（如果您使用）
JDK 6 &amp; 7 you can use the syntax below
您可以使用JDK 6和7的语法如下
so it containing at schedules annotation
因此它包含按计划注释
for other father innovations there's
对于其他父亲的创新
always a different container annotation
总是不同的容器注释
that's the best you can do until you get
那是你可以做的最好的事情，直到你得到
6 &amp; 7 of course also possible with
6和7当然也可以
spring frame at all but if you run JDK 8
弹簧框架，但如果您运行JDK 8
by all means benefit from the more the
绝对受益于更多
cleaner and more natural more expressive
更自然更自然
more readable version above
上面更具可读性的版本
right so much for Java 8 I'm going to
对于Java 8来说非常正确
show you a few other important Spring
向您展示其他一些重要的春季
Framework for container features it's
容器功能的框架
just a quick tour to give you an
只是一个快速导览，给您一个
impression of what you can follow up on
可以跟进的印象
there are many details to be discovered
有很多细节有待发现
in our reference documentation recent
在我们最近的参考文档中
blog post and so forth an important
博客帖子等等很重要
focus was on groovy still is on groovy
重点是在常规上
and one of the outcomes here is this
这里的结果之一是
definition format this is a DSL a groovy
定义格式，这是DSL的常规
based script that defines spring beans
定义Spring bean的基于脚本
it's basically similar to spring XML
它基本上类似于spring XML
bean definitions at an external
外部的bean定义
definition format saying like a Dean of
定义格式说像院长
name and type with properties passed in
名称和类型以及传入的属性
it even has support for XML namespace
它甚至支持XML名称空间
parsing this format isn't new it comes
解析这种格式不是新来的
from Grails
来自Grails
it's called the bean building in Grails
它被称为Grails中的bean建筑
we call it query based definitions in
我们称其为基于查询的定义
spring thermic 4 it's basically moving
春季热力4它基本上在移动
down from Braille to the core framework
从盲文到核心框架
and as of the next generation of Grails
从下一代Grails开始
Grails will also consume it from there
谷物也会从那里消耗掉
so there's a single place where the
所以有一个地方
system maintained but it's then
系统维护，但是
available immediately available to any
可供任何人立即使用
kind of spring based application any
一种基于弹簧的应用程序
architecture the definition format
架构定义格式
itself is pretty powerful has some
本身很强大有一些
really nice elements to it since it's
因为它是非常好的元素
fundamentally a groovy script you can do
从根本上讲，您可以做一个普通的脚本
anything that you can do in groovy you
您可以随心所欲地做任何事情
can import common classes above you can
可以在上面导入通用类
use conditional statements below so it's
在下面使用条件语句
really nice in just way more dynamic and
真的很好，只是动态性更强
flexible then then the rather rigid XML
那么灵活，然后是相当严格的XML
schema form it is but fundamental
模式形式，但这是基础
it's the same kind of configuration
这是相同的配置
style expressed in a different language
用其他语言表达的风格
at the same time groobie support
同时groobie支持
actually our intentions with groovy go
实际上，我们的意图与常规无关
much further just just for a quick
只是为了快速而已
thought right consider implementing an
正确的想法考虑实施
entire spring based application
整个基于Spring的应用程序
architecture using Ruby no dot Java
使用Ruby的Java无点Java
files using Ruby all the way long you
一直使用Ruby的文件
implement spring components regular
定期实施弹簧组件
spring components with spring
带弹簧的弹簧组件
stereotyped limitations spring
刻板的限制弹簧
configuration classes everything that
配置类的一切
you're used to everything that we've
您已经习惯了我们所拥有的一切
been showing in the state of the art
一直在展示最新技术
section before you can do that with
部分，然后才能使用
provision Scooby supports all of those
提供Scooby支持所有这些
Java language elements it's actually
实际上是Java语言元素
really sweet to try to do it
尝试做起来真是太好了
like without any shower facts involved
就像没有任何淋浴事实
you can take that pretty far and it's a
你可以走得很远，这是一个
usage model that we officially support
我们正式支持的使用模式
however in practice if you just like to
但是在实践中，如果您只想
selectively use groovy the spin
有选择地使用自旋
definition format is shown here is a
定义格式如下所示
good good starting point may be
良好的起点可能是
implementing some classes maybe just
实现一些类也许只是
your your MVC controllers using groovy
您的groovy您的MVC控制器
there are many ways to integrate some
有很多方法可以整合一些
use of groovy into spring based
将groovy应用于基于春季的
applications we also aside from the bean
除了bean之外的应用程序
definition format we care for many
我们关心的定义格式
subtle details here so there's a lot of
细微的细节在这里，所以有很多
fine-tuning that we are doing or willing
调整我们正在或愿意做的
to do towards natural support for
自然支持
growing groovy is the first class
时髦是一流的
citizen in the spring from a world right
世界右翼的春天的市民
wearing to what we've seen before as
穿着我们以前看到的
profiles as a kind of simple kind of
配置文件是一种简单的
condition for selecting specific means
选择特定手段的条件
that are to be registered with the
要在
container we have a completely reflected
容器，我们有一个完整的反映
version of this in spring from ik 4 it's
从ik 4春季发布的版本
now called a condition model like
现在称为条件模型
literally with a condition interface
字面上带有条件接口
condition context coming in and then add
条件上下文进入，然后添加
conditional annotation can basically say
条件注释基本上可以说
add conditional and you implement a
添加条件，然后实施
programmatic condition a kind of
程序性条件
callback that will be allowed to
允许的回调
evaluate whether to register again the
评估是否再次注册
annotated being at runtime there's rich
注释在运行时有丰富
context coming in you can react to
上下文进入您可以做出反应
existing beam definitions the presence
现有光束定义的存在
of specific kinds of infrastructure
特定类型的基础架构
chains before so it's a very dynamic
连锁店，所以它是一个非常动态的
model and profiles are now simply an
模型和配置文件现在只是一个
implementation of such a condition the
这种条件的执行
literally profile condition and Springs
字面条件和弹簧
at profiling notation is met annotated
在剖析符号上满足注释
with at conditional profile condition so
在条件配置文件条件下
this is
这是
of course an open model an extensible
当然，开放模型是可扩展的
model you can define your own conditions
您可以定义自己的条件的模型
you can define your own diploma styles
您可以定义自己的文凭样式
with that you can take that pretty far
这样你就可以走得更远
in the custom way but we're also at the
以自定义的方式，但我们也在
same time exploiting it in one of our
同时在我们的其中之一中利用它
sister projects that spring boot in
姐姐计划 spring boot
particular so if you look at spring
特别是如果你看着春天
boots spring boot is really
靴子 spring boot 真的
demonstrating the power of this
展示了这种力量
condition model it takes it as far as it
条件模型
can with really aggressive defaulting
可以进行真正积极的违约
wear what you're specifying is very
穿你指定的东西很
minimal
最小的
check out the spring food examples for
查看春季食物的例子
example I an NBC controller
例如我是NBC控制器
implemented in groovy you provide just
groovy实现，您只提供
the controller nothing else and you
控制器没别的，你
bootstrap it with an embedded web server
使用嵌入式Web服务器引导它
with hardly any setup around that's
几乎没有任何设置
really smart and aggressive defaulting
真正明智而激进的违约
going on here and it's based on the
继续在这里，它基于
spring from a poor condition model so
来自不良状态模型，因此
definitely check out sprinkles it's not
肯定检查洒不是
the focus of this presentation but it's
本演讲的重点，但这是
a great follow up we provided the link
很好的跟进我们提供了链接
to our new website there the spring boot
到我们的新网站那里有 spring boot
Umbridge homepage on it definitely check
在Umbridge主页上一定要检查一下
it out it went wonder though our c1 this
它出来了，尽管我们的C1这很奇怪
week spring built 100 our c1 is
一周的春天建成100我们的C1是
available
有空
alright let's return to the annotation
好吧，让我们回到注释
model for just a moment
模特片刻
a subtle but important new feature in
一个微妙但重要的新功能
spring framework for is about the use of
Spring Framework 是关于使用
annotation attributes in the composable
可组合中的注释属性
model of course you could compose your
您当然可以撰写模型
custom scope annotations or custom
自定义范围注释或自定义
transaction annotation before it was
之前的交易注释
entirely possible in spring 3 however as
完全有可能在春季3
of spring forward you can use attributes
可以使用属性的属性
you can declare attributes this my
您可以将属性声明为我的
session scoped annotation above here
上面的会话范围注释
declares a proximal attribute proxy mode
声明近端属性代理模式
of course refers to the proximity
当然是指接近
attribute in spring standard ex-cop
春季标准前警察的属性
annotation there is a proxy mode to be
注释中有一个代理模式
set there so just by convention if it's
设置在那里，按照惯例，如果它是
the same name the same named attribute
同名同名属性
it refers to the same attribute in the
它指的是相同的属性
meta notation so there's no additional
元符号，因此没有其他
set of necessary you just declare an
您必须声明一组
edge with the same name here and you
与您同名的边缘
allow uses of your custom annotation to
允许使用您的自定义注释
specify a proxy mode so it's a nice
指定代理模式，这是一个很好的选择
design element in particular if you're
设计元素，如果您
designing like a set of annotations for
设计像一组注释
an entire project thing to use as a kind
整个项目用作一种东西
of guideline for that for the guidance
指导原则
effect of it all then this feature can
这一切的效果，然后此功能就可以
become really powerful not least of it
变得非常强大，尤其是它
all because you can control not only
全部是因为您不仅可以控制
availability of attributes but also the
属性的可用性以及
default thing for such attributes look
这种属性的默认外观
at the second example my transactional
在第二个示例中，我的交易
below this one has a read-only attribute
在此下方有一个只读属性
read-only refers to the same named
只读是指相同的命名
attribute in spring substandard a
春季不合格的属性a
transactional annotation as used as a
事务注释，用作
metonym tation here read only in spring
这里的转义词仅在春季读
standard annotation has a default of
标准注释的默认值为
false so if you're not specifying it
假，所以如果您不指定它
there are no read-only characteristics
没有只读特征
apply the custom my transactional
应用我的交易习惯
annotation that we're seeing here has a
我们在这里看到的注释有一个
read-only attribute without a default
只读属性，无默认值
according to Java annotation rules this
根据Java注释规则，
means that the the value has to be
表示该值必须为
specified so every user of your my
指定了您的我的每个用户
transaction annotation every time it's
每次交易注释
used you need to specify read-only
用过的你需要指定只读
equals true or read-only equals false
等于true或只读等于false
this is actually an intentional feature
这实际上是一个故意的功能
here you can use this for the guidance
在这里您可以使用它作为指导
effect of it all where you say like
您所说的所有效果
I want uses of that annotation to reason
我想使用该注释进行推理
about the read on the status of the
关于阅读状态
transaction I want them to be explicit
我希望他们明确的交易
about it to think about it and to
关于它思考和
specify the correct flag value well if
如果正确指定正确的标志值
it's defaulted they may forget about it
默认情况下，他们可能会忘记它
they're not seeing it right so here by
他们没有看到正确的，所以在这里
not declaring a default you're forcing
没有声明您要强制使用默认值
them to think about it at the specified
他们考虑在指定的时间
so that's over writable attributes and
这样就超过了可写属性
the users defaulting with override apply
默认使用替代的用户适用
tributes a really nice addition to the
贡献了一个非常好的补充
composable annotation model in spring
春天的可组合注释模型
let's revisit another part of our model
让我们回顾一下模型的另一部分
which is the matching between injection
这是注射之间的匹配
points and definition points what we see
点和定义点我们所看到的
above is our maipo between service in
以上是我们在服务之间的maipo
this version here it takes a my
这个版本在这里需要我的
repository generically declare for
仓库一般声明
account let's assume my repository is an
帐户，假设我的存储库是
interface and has a type variable for
接口，并具有类型变量
the entity type that it manages this
它管理的实体类型
became pretty common over the years so
多年来变得很普遍，所以
we are seeing that quite often lately
我们最近经常看到
our own spring data system projects has
我们自己的 spring data 系统项目有
a repository model very much like that
像这样的存储库模型
so for such a model there are typically
因此，对于这种模型，通常
multiple implementations of the
的多种实现
repository interface in the system
系统中的存储库接口
registered at the same time so if the
同时注册，因此如果
injection point says I want in my
注射点说我要在我的
repository for account what the
帐户存储什么
container does is goes through all
容器所做的一切
matches by primary type so all my
按主要类型匹配，所以我所有
repositories and then it tries to find
存储库，然后尝试查找
one where the generic the full generic
一种泛型，全泛型
type declaration actually matches so it
类型声明实际上匹配，所以它
says like among the my repositories is
说像我的存储库中是
the one that specifically generically
特别是一般的
declared for account if yes that's our
声明为帐户，如果是，那是我们的
match if only a single one is requested
如果只请求一个，则匹配
and as you can see here it's both the
如您所见，这两者都是
parameter above the constructor
构造函数上方的参数
parameter declared for my repository
为我的存储库声明的参数
account and it's also an HB methods
帐户，这也是HB方法
typically to be found in a different
通常在其他地方找到
part of the system right somewhere in
系统的一部分，就在
the configuration class that method is
该方法是的配置类
also declared for my repository bracket
也为我的存储库支架声明了
account in its return type here
此处返回类型的帐户
for spring to be able to resolve this
春天才能解决这个问题
the information needs to be stored
信息需要存储
somewhere so it needs to be in the
某个地方，所以它需要在
method signature as shown below or it
方法签名如下所示
needs to be in the extent or implement
需要在范围或实施上
signature of an implementation for us so
为我们实现的签名
it's also sufficient for like my account
对于我的帐户来说也足够了
repository input class to say implements
要实现的存储库输入类
my repository bracket account in its in
我在其存储库中的支架帐户
its declaration so as long as that
它的声明只要
information this specific generic
此特定泛型信息
information is somewhere in the method
信息在方法中
signature of a vector II method or in
向量II方法的签名或
the implementation class hierarchy we
实现类层次结构
are able to find it and we are able to
能够找到它，我们能够
use it for matching purposes even if
将其用于匹配目的，即使
there are several my repository so we
我的仓库有几个，所以我们
always select the right one that's a
总是选择正确的
spring framework for feature in spring
春季特性框架
from act three the generic type II would
从第三幕起，第二类通用
have been ignored we just have looked at
被忽略，我们只是看着
my repository we would have said that
我的仓库我们会说
several my repository is matching it's
我的几个存储库与之匹配
not unique you need to add additional
不是唯一的，您需要添加其他
metadata so in spring three you would
元数据，因此在春季三
have had to add a qualifier like qualify
必须添加像qualify这样的限定词
account above at the constructor level
构造函数级别的以上帐户
and also at the admin level with spring
以及春季的管理员级别
from a course capability of fully
从完全的课程能力
matching generic type structures no such
匹配通用类型结构没有这样的
qualifies unnecessary as long as the
只要没有资格
type declaration itself is expressive
类型声明本身就是表达性的
enough it's also more readable for a
足够使它更具可读性
start if you have qualifiers string
如果您有限定词，则开始
qualifies next to it that's really not
排在它旁边的那不是真的
as expressive and not as readable as
表现力强而不可读
this version areas so again it's also
这个版本领域再次如此
about readability of the source code and
关于源代码的可读性，以及
about not repeating yourself
关于不重复自己
all right further continue refinements
可以继续完善
I just like to quickly point them out
我只是想快速指出他们
here so they're all in our what's new
在这里，所以他们都在我们的最新消息中
section and in the reference
部分和参考中
documentation but there's quite a bit
文档，但有很多
more that we do in the container space
我们在集装箱领域所做的更多工作
for example you can explain an injection
例如您可以解释注射
point with at lazy which now means for
指向懒惰，这意味着
this specific injection point you want a
您想要一个特定的注入点
lazy initialization proxy you want the
您想要的惰性初始化代理
proxy implementing your declared type
代理实现您声明的类型
lazily referring to a spring target beam
懒惰地指的是弹簧目标梁
that's basically what you could do
那基本上就是你可以做的
before with the so called provider
之前与所谓的提供商
interface provider off account
接口提供商帐户关闭
repository with a get method every time
每次都使用get方法存储库
you call in to get methods we actually
您调用以获得我们实际使用的方法
grab an object from the container so
从容器中抓取一个物体
they were there was something like the
他们在那里
possible before but with that lazy it's
可能之前有过，但是懒惰的是
now a proxy no get method to be called
现在将调用代理no get方法
the proxy implementing an interface
代理实现接口
typically or a target class proxy and be
通常是目标类代理，并且是
every call to that proxy is being
对该代理的每次调用
delegated to the actual target instance
委托给实际的目标实例
only when the call comes in so it's a
只有当电话打进来的时候
bit like a stroke to proxy but it's
有点像中风的代理，但这是
primarily for resolving more complex
主要用于解决更复杂的问题
dependency arrangements within a larger
较大范围内的依赖安排
set of single teens for example where a
例如，单身青少年组
component can explicitly say I want a
组件可以明确地说我想要一个
reference to that beam but I don't need
提到那个光束，但我不需要
to use it immediately so I'm saying as
立即使用它，所以我说
lazy and I only want it to be there I
懒惰，我只希望它在那里
only require to be there once I start
只要我开始就必须在那里
invoking methods on it that's what
调用方法就是这样
you're saying when you're saying it auto
你是说自动的时候
light as lazy so that's that's a nice
像懒惰一样轻盈，那是一个很好的选择
variant of something that was possible
可能的事物的变体
before but they smell syntactic
以前但是他们闻到句法
synthetically nice and most presses then
综合性很好，那时大多数印刷机
all the variants would have been
所有的变体
we can also for injection points accept
我们也可以为注射点接受
the rate and lists we always could do
我们总是可以做到的价格和清单
that so that's an existing feature but
那是现有功能，但是
now we can inject that in pre-ordered
现在我们可以预购
form using Springs or that interface or
使用Springs或该接口的表格，或
at all the annotation if the target
如果目标是所有注释
beans
豆子
basically comply with those ordering
基本上符合那些订购
rules we pre order them before injecting
规则，我们在注射之前先订购它们
the array lists nice fine tuning right
数组列出了很好的微调权
you get it in preview ordered form
您以预览订购的形式获得它
instead of having to sort them
不必对它们进行排序
yourselves and a nice enabling feature
自己和一个不错的启用功能
as well we were talking about proxies
我们也在谈论代理
and type of class proxies for target
目标的类别代理的类型和类型
class proxies as of spring for you can
您可以在春季使用类代理
declare a target class proxy without
声明目标类代理，而无需
having to provide the default
必须提供默认值
constructor previously you had to do
以前必须要做的构造函数
that for target class proxies for
用于目标类代理的
interface proxies you were free to have
您可以自由使用的界面代理
any construct arrangement but for a
除了
target target class proxy where we're
目标目标类代理我们在哪里
using the the implementation class
使用实现类
itself for the proxy instance as well
本身也适用于代理实例
you had to have a default constructor
你必须有一个默认的构造函数
just for that proxy for the ability to
只是为了代理的能力
use it that class as a proxy class that
使用该类作为代理类
restriction has gone away now it's we
限制已经消失，现在是我们
are using the objectives library to
正在使用目标库
create proxy instances now target across
创建代理实例现在跨
proxy instances without invoking any
代理实例而不调用任何实例
constructor because that's fundamentally
构造函数，因为从根本上讲
the correct thing to do there is a
正确的做法是
target instance that's that's the
目标实例就是
instant that contains the state that's
包含状态的瞬间
the instance that where the constructor
构造函数所在的实例
invocation is relevant for the proxy the
调用与代理有关
class is just a template of method
类只是方法的模板
signatures basically it's it's
签名基本上是
semantically correct to not invoke a
语义上正确，不调用
constructor there so that's exactly what
那里的构造函数，这就是
we're doing now one of the effects is
我们现在正在做的效果之一是
you can use any constructor Arrangements
您可以使用任何构造函数
on your target classes so you can use
在您的目标课程上，以便您可以使用
constructor injection whatever you
构造函数注入
prefer no need for default constructor
不需要默认构造函数
anymore
不再
you
您
in the composite lamentation space we
在复合感叹空间中
extended the current possibility to the
将当前可能性扩展到
test context annotations in the test
测试中的测试上下文注释
context framework there are several
上下文框架有几种
annotations actually a few further ones
注释实际上还有一些
three of them listed here they can also
他们三个在这里列出，他们也可以
be used in the composable form now
现在以可组合形式使用
building your realm using Springs
使用Springs建立您的领域
annotations as meta annotations and last
注释作为元注释和最后
but not least in this little further
但同样重要的是
further refinement list there's time
进一步完善清单的时间
zone management so in spring there's
区域管理，所以在春季
existing infrastructure to manage a
现有基础架构来管理
locale the local context resolver
locale本地上下文解析器
already existed in spring embassy data
春季使馆数据中已经存在
the pale context holder at a lower level
较低级别的苍白上下文持有者
in the framework where different parts
在不同部分的框架中
of the framework and different parts of
框架的不同部分
your application can refer to
您的应用程序可以参考
essentially manage the helper thread
本质上管理助手线程
spring MVC would set that for every
Spring MVC将为每个
request this existing infrastructure has
要求此现有基础结构具有
been extended to cover time zones hardly
几乎没有扩展到时区
forges a310 support and total time
争取a310的支持和总时间
support so those immediately consume
支持，使那些立即消耗
such a managed time zone so in addition
这样的时区，另外
to setting a specific locale for each
为每个设置特定的语言环境
request you can also rely on setting a
要求您还可以依靠设置
specific time zone if you provide the
如果您提供特定的时区
appropriate rules for it
适当的规则
so much for container refinements at
这么多的容器精炼
this point I'd like to extend our
这一点我想扩展我们的
coverage a little bit towards the middle
覆盖范围向中间一点
where space and a really important topic
空间和一个非常重要的话题
in in spring from book 4 is WebSockets
从书4春季开始的是WebSockets
and our WebSocket support comes in
我们的WebSocket支持进来了
basically at two levels there's native
基本上有两个层次
WebSocket support raw WebSocket support
WebSocket支持原始WebSocket支持
where you interact with the framework
您与框架互动的地方
and with the communication model at the
并在
raw socket level but the more
原始套接字级别，但更多
interesting part from my perspective is
在我看来，有趣的部分是
that we support higher level messaging
我们支持更高级别的消息传递
protocols on top so at that point this
协议在最上面，所以在这一点上
really turns into a message oriented
真的变成了面向消息的
architecture it turns into a messaging
架构变成了消息传递
style what we provide with springtime
春季我们提供的风格
look for oh here for the reason is a
在这里寻找哦，原因是
combination of all those things a
所有这些东西的结合
low-level WebSocket infrastructure with
具有以下功能的低级WebSocket基础结构
a socket is fallback option where you
套接字是备用选项
can use WebSocket style communication
可以使用WebSocket样式进行通讯
even for scenarios where actual web
即使是在实际网络中
server communication is impossible but
服务器通讯是不可能的，但是
some live browsers don't support it
一些实时浏览器不支持
there's an a natural sake as for the
有一个自然的缘故
option that can be easily configured so
可以轻松配置的选项
we provide a foundational WebSocket
我们提供了基础的WebSocket
support layer we also provide a general
支持层我们也提供一般
messaging module with rules and
带有规则的消息传递模块和
annotations and types for general
通用注释和类型
messaging endpoints support for simple
消息传递端点支持简单
messaging protocols goes with it in
消息传递协议随之而来
particular for this common stumped
特别是对于这个普通的树桩
protocol and we also support the
协议，我们也支持
combination stomp basically as a
组合脚基本上作为
messaging layer on top of web socket
Web套接字顶部的消息传递层
communication channels so this is really
沟通渠道，所以这真的
really interesting stuff because it's an
非常有趣的东西，因为它是
enabler for a completely different kind
完全不同的促成因素
of application architecture very
应用程序架构的
messaging oriented completely different
面向消息传递完全不同
kind of communication style even if you
那种沟通方式，即使你
are building a web application so we
正在构建一个Web应用程序，所以我们
this is a work area in spring where a
这是春天的工作区，
lot of effort went into just great
付出很大的努力
coverage from my colleague Rossum in
我的同事罗森（Rossum）的报道
terms of lock post and if you recorded
锁杆的条款以及是否已记录
talks where he goes really deep into the
谈到他真正深入的地方
design and practically using usage
设计和实际使用
considerations here
这里的注意事项
this very much is in line with a spring
这非常符合春天
force mission to support concurrent
强制任务支持并发
processing architectures messaging
处理架构消息传递
architectures but also asynchronous
架构，但也异步
processing of any kind and in deadlines
在期限内进行任何形式的处理
we for example also provide an async
例如，我们还提供了一个异步
rest template where for any invocations
休息模板在哪里任何调用
you actually get the fugitive ex
你实际上得到了逃犯
listenable future back you don't have to
可听的未来，您不必
synchronously wait for the result to
同步等待结果
come in so you can also define HTTP
进来，所以您也可以定义HTTP
direction layers in an asynchronous
异步中的方向层
style using using DET async rest
使用DET异步休息样式
template but that's just an additional
模板，但这只是一个附加
note I'd like to show you just a quick
请注意，我只想向您展示
example for how how WebSockets feel like
WebSockets感觉如何的示例
at a row level this is WebSockets at the
在行级别上，这是WebSockets
hands of level raw WebSocket Handler see
级别的原始WebSocket处理程序之手
the website at hand interface it's
手头的网站界面
basically a WebSocket session in the raw
基本上是原始的WebSocket会话
WebSocket message coming in it's
WebSocket消息进来了
physically unstructured no specific
身体无组织，无特定
protocol implied what you can see above
协议暗示您可以在上面看到
is a spring configuration class in this
在这是一个Spring 配置类
case even a specific role it configures
甚至配置它的特定角色
WebSocket handlers it registers a
WebSocket处理程序注册
handler against the registry and through
处理程序对注册表并通过
a little with sock GS additional
袜子GS额外一点
statement up there it even allows
甚至在那里声明
Socrates vortex to be immediately
苏格拉底旋涡要立即
available that's all you need to do to
这就是您需要做的所有工作
enable success for decks here the so
在这里使甲板成功
that's that's basically working at the
那基本上就是在
raw WebSocket level from a messaging
来自消息传递的原始WebSocket级别
perspective this is what you would
角度来看这就是你想要的
typically do a controller and endpoint
通常做一个控制器和端点
arrangement with methods in the method
方法中的方法排列
level annotations that met incoming
符合传入的级别注释
messages against specific methods for
针对特定方法的消息
example the message mapping for trade
交易消息映射示例
below accepts a specific specific
以下接受特定
messages from an incoming destination
来自传入目的地的消息
from a specific destination here the
从这里的特定目的地
incoming messages are mapped onto a
传入消息被映射到
trade payload object pre converted
贸易有效载荷对象已预先转换
passed into the method very similar to
传递给方法非常类似于
spring MVC style controllers in
中的Spring MVC样式控制器
particular to spring web control of the
特别是对Spring Web Control的
process rest style okay
工艺休息风格还可以
they really look very similar here but
他们在这里看起来真的很相似，但是
instead of mapping to specific HTTP
而不是映射到特定的HTTP
endpoints we're mapping to specific
我们正在映射到特定的端点
message destinations here or to specific
此处或特定的消息目的地
kinds of events such as subscribe events
诸如订阅事件之类的事件
in some protocol in nine in the method
在某些方法中，在九种方法中
above the endpoint mode is very similar
端点模式以上非常相似
statistically to spring MSE controllers
统计到弹簧MSE控制器
you can even combine it with spring MVC
您甚至可以将其与Spring MVC结合使用
controllers if you prefer so
控制器，如果您愿意的话
so that's just that just a quick a quick
所以就这么快
example to give you some some idea of
例子给你一些想法
what Springs message oriented
Springs消息导向的内容
architecture model is about with its
体系结构模型与其有关
specific support for stump and
对树桩的特殊支持
WebSockets the soft jazz fallback it's a
WebSockets柔和的爵士后备
it's a really comprehensive arrangement
这是一个非常全面的安排
even at this very point
即使在这一点上
all right to wrap up a few notes on
可以在上面写一些笔记
three things this Java EE 7 we generally
这个Java EE 7的三件事我们通常
support the Java EE 7 level of
支持Java EE 7级别
specifications in spring from buffer oh
缓冲的弹簧规格哦
and the most important ones are listed
列出了最重要的
here
这里
the ones with relevant some on spring
与春季相关的一些
the JMS - Oh update isn't particularly
JMS-更新不是特别重要
exciting it's basically the first JMS
令人兴奋的是，这基本上是第一个JMS
version to be released since 2002 when
自2002年起发布的版本
GMS wanted one came out so it's really
GMS想要一个出来，所以真的
really over to you but what's actually
真的交给了你，但实际上是什么
in there is more likely obvious nothing
那里更可能没有明显的东西
particularly exciting however if you run
特别令人兴奋的是，如果您跑步
against the dreamers to a provider
针对提供者的梦想者
springs JMS support auto detects it and
springs JMS支持自动检测到它并
supports a few additional jamester tool
支持一些额外的jamester工具
features here such as delivery delays
交货延迟等功能
for example with GTA 1 or 2 there's an
例如，对于GTA 1或2，
annotation coming with it that can be
附带的注释可以是
used as an alternative to Springs
用作弹簧的替代品
transaction limitation if you prefer a
如果您更喜欢交易限制
standard annotation there a Java
Java有标准注释
external tation they're automatically
外在的态度，他们是自动的
detected by Springs are no specific set
没有检测到由Springs检测到的特定集合
of necessary to use that may be the most
最有必要使用的
common of these here is JPA to that one
这些的共同之处是JPA
if you're upgrading to having at full of
如果您要升级到完全
three that's JPA to one provider spring
JPA给一个提供商的三个春天
framework for comes with full
完整的框架
out-of-the-box approach with JP 81 not
JP 81的即用型方法不是
survive in it for the three in
在其中生存三个
particular now in the current folder
现在特别在当前文件夹中
dawood one release that's what we fully
dawood一个版本，这就是我们的全部
support is the actual cabinet for the 3G
支持才是3G的真正机柜
a version and its little peculiarities
版本及其小特性
with bean validation one that one we
通过bean验证，那一个我们
also to mine up that really to the
也要真正挖掘到
communication spectacled we support
我们支持沟通交流
hibernate validator 5 $2 as its
休眠验证器5 $ 2作为其
reference implementation if you consider
如果您考虑参考实施
upgrading to having it validate the 5
升级以验证5
todo spring framework for comes without
要做的todo Spring Framework
full out-of-the-box reports for it for
完整的现成报告
the first time and jasa 2 3 6 also worth
第一次和贾莎2 3 6也值得
a note here it's a bit of a different
这里的笔记有点不同
kind of specs but we supported in an
某种规格，但我们在
interesting way GSR 2 through 6 is a
GSR 2到6的有趣方式是
kind of extension of the Java util
Java util的一种扩展
concurrent executive service model and
并发执行服务模型和
what we're doing spring is get our
我们在春天做的是得到我们的
standard executive service support
标准行政服务支持
basically are the adapters that we
基本上是我们的适配器
already ship for Springs task scheduler
已经为Springs Task Scheduler发货
model and task executor model on to Java
Java上的模型和任务执行器模型
to con crime if you set them up they
如果您将其设置为犯罪
automatically detect whether they are
自动检测它们是否
interacting with which is there's a two
与之交互的有两个
three six compliance extended executive
三六合规行政长官
service and if they do so they translate
服务，如果他们这样做，他们会翻译
your incoming requests incoming calls
您的来电请求来电
onto the best possible representation so
尽可能做到最好
if they're on Jase are two three six and
如果他们在Jase上，则是2 3 6
what you what you specify coming in here
你指定的是什么
is a cron trigger we translate it onto a
是cron触发器，我们将其转换为
chaser two three six trigger if that's
追逐者二三六触发如果
not available we have a different code
不可用，我们有不同的代码
path that takes a regular executive
需要定期执行的路径
service and processes the trigger
服务并处理触发器
manually so we try to interact with the
手动操作，因此我们尝试与
target platform at the target threat
目标平台面对目标威胁
school in the best possible form that's
以最好的形式
particularly interesting on a
特别有趣
forward-looking note we're managed
我们管理的前瞻性说明
environments both Java EE 7 service but
同时使用Java EE 7服务和
also cloud platforms and so forth would
还有云平台等等
expose GS a 2 3 6 compliant thread pools
公开GS a 2 3 6兼容线程池
through an executive service model and
通过执行服务模型
spring framework for automatically
Spring Framework 自动
consumes them if pointed to it it also
消费他们，如果指向它也
detects them and uses them in the best
检测它们并以最佳方式使用它们
possible way
可能的方式
and that really an important enabler for
这确实是促进
asynchronous processing architectures
异步处理架构
when you're running in a managed
在托管环境中运行时
environment write down the same down the
环境写下来一样
same perspective let's look at target
以相同的角度来看目标
service here's just a summary which can
服务这里只是一个摘要，可以
also be found on our migrations page on
也可以在我们的迁移页面上找到
github of a recommended server versions
推荐服务器版本的github
there's a bit of a change in our policy
我们的政策有些变化
here technically we have minimum system
从技术上讲，我们的系统最少
requirements and you can deploy a spring
需求，您可以部署 Spring
forward application anywhere where those
将申请转发到任何地方
minimum requirements are match however
最低要求是匹配的
from a support perspective from a
从支持角度看
reproduction perspective if you have
复制角度（如果有）
been initiative us we request to be at
是我们主动提出的要求
least at a reasonably recent maintenance
至少在合理的近期维护中
level of each of these servers so you if
每个服务器的级别，因此您如果
you're deploying to tomcat 6 - though
您正在部署到tomcat 6-尽管
that's the server to the 5 server that's
这是服务器到5个服务器
fine but please at least use a
很好，但请至少使用一个
reasonably recent maintenance version of
最新的维护版本
target there as listed here the same
与此处列出的目标相同
applies to like jetty and so forth we
适用于码头等
also support WebSphere 7 for example as
还支持WebSphere 7，例如
long as you're on 709 with the j/p HRO
只要您使用j / p HRO在709上
feature peg you're fully covered spring
功能钉，您完全遮住了弹簧
framework for applications deployed just
刚部署的应用程序框架
fine that's an important deployment
很好，这是重要的部署
target for spring and of course web the
春季的目标，当然还有网络
8:00 and 8:05 work just fine as well
8:00和8:05也很好
on WebLogic at least if you're at least
至少如果您至少在WebLogic上
on 10.32 4 with the JP 800
JP 800在10.32 4上
feature installed then spring for
安装功能，然后弹簧
applications deploy just fine even if
应用程序即使部署也很好
they are using GA PA this page also
他们也在使用GA PA此页面
lists where WebSockets are being
列出WebSocket所在的位置
supported and on a particularly
支持和特别
interesting note
有趣的笔记
WebSockets support standard chaser 2 3 5
WebSockets支持标准追赶者2 3 5
6 compliant WebSockets support has been
已有6种兼容的WebSockets支持
beg ported to Tomcat 7 o 47 and higher
乞求移植到Tomcat 7 o 47及更高版本
you don't need to upgrade to tanka date
您不需要升级到短途约会
to have WebSockets some get 7 o 47
使WebSockets得到7 o 47
entire is sufficient we supported on
整个就足够了
song to date as well of course I'm JD 9
当然，我也是JD 9
o and TD 9 1s offspring from abroad for
o和来自国外的TD 9 1s后代
that oh that one
那个那个那个
we also support wildlife WebSockets on
我们还支持野生动物WebSockets
wild fly which is the next generation of
野蝇是下一代
the Kapus application server
Kapus应用程序服务器
on a related note for third-party
有关第三方的注释
libraries such as high vanity education
虚荣教育等图书馆
Court sense for we have a policy now
法院判断，因为我们现在有一项政策
where we're supporting a three year
我们支持三年
range back from any given spring
从任何给定的春天开始
preparation the den current versions of
准备当前版本的
of each library we would still support
我们仍将支持的每个图书馆
so at this point that means concretely
所以在这一点上，这意味着
that we support having a three to six
我们支持三到六
and higher still education to one and
并接受更高的高等教育
higher courts one eight and higher but
高等法院八分之一以上
this is going to raise quite soon
这将很快提高
- eh cash to the five and higher courts
-现金给五个及更高级别的法院
to low and higher checks until Ohio for
接受较低和较高的支票，直到俄亥俄州
example having a three to six support we
有三到六个支持的示例
will probably preserve for a long time
可能会保存很长时间
since it's so common out there so that's
因为那里很普通所以
it's a bit of a policy change where we
这是一项政策更改，
don't support the party libraries way
不支持聚会图书馆的方式
back into history we supporting three
回到历史，我们支持三个
years back in history basically as a
基本上可以追溯到几年前
simple guidance rule these specific
这些具体的简单指导规则
versions can be checked on our
版本可以在我们的网站上查看
migrations patient in the documentation
文档中的迁移患者
so we are already in upgrade
所以我们已经在升级
considerations basically here's the link
注意事项基本上是链接
in the middle here's the link to the
在中间，这是指向
magnet to that migration page on github
对github上的迁移页面具有吸引力
if you'd like to check out some details
如果您想查看一些详细信息
generally speaking we strongly recommend
一般来说，我们强烈建议
an upgrade to spring framework for if
如果没有，请升级到Spring Framework
you are considering the use of Java 8
您正在考虑使用Java 8
language features this is basically
语言特征这基本上是
mandatory if you're on GDK 6 &amp; 7 it's
如果您使用的是GDK 6和7，则必须使用
strongly recommended Spring Framework 3
强烈推荐Spring Framework 3
the 2 is in maintenance mode already so
2已经处于维护模式
it's good it's it's going to see a 3 to
很好，这将是看到3
7 release on Monday so it's actively
周一7发布，因此它很活跃
maintained it's kept at a very recent
保持它是最近的
level supports many recent little things
水平支持许多最近的小事情
still but fundamentally it's in
仍然但从根本上讲
maintenance mode new features are going
维护模式新功能即将推出
to be seen in this sort of X line Omni
在这种X线Omni上可以看到
we have two folded orders one release
我们有两个折叠订单，一个版本
coming up on Monday we have afforded
星期一就要来了
order to release scheduled right after
下订单后立即发布
OpenJDK hga in late march so that's
OpenJDK hga将于3月下旬发布，因此
where physically little features can
物理上很少有功能的地方
come in will come in in some form still
进来还会以某种形式进来
as 3 2 X I'm turns into a basically a
当3 2 X我变成一个基本上
straight maintenance mode from 3 to 7
直接维护模式从3到7
onwards on a forward-looking note into
从前瞻性角度来看
to conclude this theorem let me just
总结这个定理，让我
quickly talk about our Spring Framework
快速谈论我们的Spring Framework
all at one time the most interesting
一次都最有趣
part is we have a shorter iteration plan
部分是我们有一个较短的迭代计划
so for that one is actually already on
所以对于那个已经在
the horizon we intend to have a release
我们打算发布的地平线
candidate ready in June and we intend to
候选人在六月准备好了，我们打算
be generally available with it in August
在八月份可以普遍使用
so it's an 8 month duration from spring
从春季到现在有8个月的时间
for mackerel there's quite a quite a few
鲭鱼有很多
themes plan 4x web resource handling
主题计划4倍Web资源处理
maybe one of the most important ones
也许是最重要的之一
where we had many requests from many
我们有很多人的要求
sides for refined features in the cache
侧面用于缓存中的精细功能
in the HTTP cache control for resource
在资源的HTTP缓存控件中
pipelining there are many related little
流水线有很多相关的小
features that add up to hopefully truly
这些功能加起来有望真正实现
comprehensive web Crystal sampling that
全面的网络水晶采样
we're working on to
我们正在努力
to the foldable on target here we intend
到这里的可折叠目标
to revisit our caching support since the
自从
che cache wanted our specification is
che cache希望我们的规格是
about to go final it's in final draft
即将进行最终定稿
and it's all went through but they just
这一切都经历了，但他们只是
didn't release it yet so we're going to
还没有发布，所以我们要
align with it likely going to support a
与它保持一致可能会支持
set of annotations going to extend our
一组注释将扩展我们的
che cache spi support which we already
che cache spi支持，我们已经
have and we're also going to add a few
有，我们还将添加一些
user requested enhancements to Springs
用户要求对Springs进行增强
on caching model a JMS overall is really
在缓存模型上，JMS总体上确实是
view we intend to a language with our
认为我们打算与我们的语言
messaging module allowing you to use the
消息传递模块，使您可以使用
the endpoint style that we've seen that
我们已经看到的端点样式
been defined by our messaging module the
由我们的消息传递模块定义
simple endpoint style for simple
简单的端点样式
messaging purposes to bind the to GMs
消息传递目的以将GM绑定到
brokers so that's a key working area for
经纪人，所以这是
spring traffic for that one and we
那个人的春天交通，我们
generally have a focus on performance
通常关注表现
improvements the idea here is that we
改进这里的想法是，我们
are going to I to work on specific areas
要去我在特定领域工作
of improvement such as for example the
诸如
use of spell expressions compiling spell
使用咒语表达来编译咒语
expressions on the fly at runtime down
表达式在运行时快速下降
to bytecode is an interesting experiment
字节码是一个有趣的实验
for heavy use of spell expressions and
大量使用咒语和
to improve starter performance where we
改善入门者的表现
can in particular towards starting up
特别是可以启动
more expensive party middleware so
比较昂贵的聚会中间件
there's there are quite a few work areas
有很多工作区
where we are comfortable with to deliver
我们乐于交付的地方
the release candidate in tune here the
在此发布的候选版本
gentle out at the next iteration is also
在下一次迭代中也要柔和
going to be about 8 months so that would
大约需要8个月的时间
be Spring Framework photo 2 in like
像是Spring Framework photo 2
April 2015
2015年4月
alright so much for this tool thanks for
好了，这个工具非常感谢
all your attention here are a few
您所有的注意力都在这里
further pointers as I mentioned check
我提到的其他指针检查
out spring boot there's our new spring
spring boot 有我们的新春天
that i/o website with a brand-new spring
具有全新春季的I / O网站
frame accomplished actually some nice
框架实际上完成了一些不错的
information how to grab the latest
信息如何获取最新
snapshot so if you're up for it
快照，因此如果您愿意
give the latest springtime box folder
提供最新的Spring box文件夹
daughters want snapshot a try it's
女儿想要快照尝试
basically a release candidate snapshots
基本上是发布候选快照
for what's going to become publicly
因为将会公开
available on Monday so feel free to give
星期一有空，请随时给
it a try our website contains the Navin
尝试一下，我们的网站包含Navin
coordinates for it
它的坐标
and there are quite a few channels where
并且有很多渠道
we publish presentations and webinars
我们发布演示文稿和网络研讨会
like this one so there's a lot to follow
像这样一个，所以有很多后续
up on thanks for staying on the line for
谢谢您一直在线
so long it's been a long presentation
这么长时间的介绍
there are maybe a question or two that
可能有一个或两个问题
we can pick up on audio channel still
我们仍然可以在音频通道上接听
yes especially if quick look yeah there
是的，尤其是如果快速浏览耶
I think there's there's just one that I
我认为我只有一个
that I thought might be good for you to
我认为可能对你有好处
comment on I think all the others have
评论，我认为其他所有人都有
been answered on because it might do
被回答，因为它可能会
some justice to those people that are
对那些
having the spring vs. or spring and Java
拥有spring vs.或spring和Java
EE debate
EE辩论
it's about CDI right after Sina the
关于新浪之后的CDI
question yep the question is can I use
是的问题是我可以使用
CGI context and dependency injection in
CGI上下文和依赖项注入
my vacations I suppose there's a
我的假期我想有一个
question and then like in BEC spring
问题，然后像在BEC春季
oriented applications fundamentally CGI
面向应用程序从根本上讲CGI
is defines its own kind of framework
定义了自己的框架
it's very much a kind of component
这是一个非常重要的组成部分
framework for the platform in many ways
该平台的框架有很多方面
so it's a it's a it's a kind of complete
所以这是一个完整的
component framework in its own right
组件框架本身
that's what it's Amy to be if you have
那就是如果你有艾米的话
some CGI usage in some applications I
一些应用程序中的一些CGI用法
mean all the power to you all right
意味着所有力量都可以
whatever works solve the problem it
不管用什么解决问题
integrates nicely with Spring Darrow
与Spring Darrow完美集成
couple of bridges available if or if
几个桥是否可用
there's if there are separate systems
是否有单独的系统
that have like rest endpoints to
像其他端点一样
communicate then then you wouldn't even
交流，那么你甚至都不会
be necessary to do actual component
做实际组件是必要的
integration at there are many ways to
整合有很多方法
combine those technologies but
结合那些技术，但是
fundamentally the spring programming and
从根本上说，Spring编程和
configuration model is a completely
配置模型是完全
comprehensive model in its own right we
本身就有综合模型
selectively integrates standard
有选择地整合标准
annotations as you've seen GSR 334
如您所见GSR 334
dependency injection chaser 303 could be
依赖注入追踪器303可以是
invalidation the JTA a 1.2 transactional
使JTA 1.2事务无效
annotation there are many standardized
注释有很多标准化
annotations being integrated into
批注已集成到
Springs programming and configuration
弹簧编程和配置
model so if you look at like a typical
模型，所以，如果你看起来像一个典型的
CGI component is a typical spring
CGI组件是典型的弹簧
component they're going to look somewhat
组件，他们将看起来有些
similar but the closer you look the more
相似，但越看越近
differences you're going to find in
您将发现的差异
spring components
弹簧组件
almost always have a stereotype and they
几乎总是有一个刻板印象，他们
are being detected by stereotype in in
被in中的构造型检测到
CDI component usually don't have a
CDI组件通常没有
stereotype they are being detected by
被他们检测到的刻板印象
presence in a jar file so it starts with
存在于jar文件中，因此它以
the bootstrapping rules and it only goes
自举规则，它只会走
from there there are many differences in
从那里有很多差异
the details semantic differences
细节语义差异
ballistic differences conceptual
弹道差异概念
differences and so from that perspective
差异等等
if you're familiar with CDI I'm sure
如果您熟悉CDI，我确定
you'll find yourself familiar in the
您会发现自己对
spring programming model initially but
春季编程模型，但
keep in mind spring has many wastes many
请记住，春天有很多浪费
ways of its own for good reasons and to
有充分的理由拥有自己的方式
use spring basically in its in its most
基本上在最大的程度上使用spring
comprehensive and convincing form I
全面而令人信服的表格I
would strongly recommend to use it
强烈建议使用它
according to the two typical spring
根据两个典型的弹簧
recommendations that's where the power
建议就是力量所在
shows through that's where the
显示通过那是
readability effect to your source code
对源代码的可读性影响
really shows through so we are really
真的显示出来，所以我们真的
trying hard as hard as we can for that
为此我们尽力而为
to be to be a comprehensive and just
成为一个全面而公正的人
clean in in its own right so that's that
自行清洁，就是这样
if the question is basically about how
如果问题基本上是关于
do you get the best possible experience
你得到最好的体验吗
using spring that's what I would
我会用春天
recommend Springs programming and
推荐Springs编程和
configuration model as the primary
配置模型为主
perspective you're getting thanks so
观点，你会得到感谢，所以
much for that um I think that's pretty
对于那个嗯，我认为这很漂亮
much it we answered all the other
我们已经回答了很多
questions in the chat so and we're
聊天中的问题，所以我们
revved up we're almost at an hour and a
振作起来，我们快一个小时了
half here so thank you for your heroic
一半在这里，谢谢你的英勇
for repetitions of this webinar and
对于此网络研讨会的重复
you're welcome I just fit very much yes
不客气，我非常适合
thank you I just want to invite everyone
谢谢，我只想邀请所有人
on the phone that there's actually still
在电话上实际上还有
quite a number of people on the line
很多人在线
looks like there's so you know hundred
好像有，所以你知道一百
plus folks we are having a great webinar
加上我们有一个很棒的网络研讨会
next month February 11th Stuart Williams
下个月2月11日Stuart Williams
and Apache Tomcat committer is going to
和Apache Tomcat的提交者将
be joined by Daniel Nicholas oh and
丹尼尔·尼古拉斯（Daniel Nicholas）也加入了
they're going to be talking about
他们将要谈论
introduction doing an introduction to
引言
Apache Tomcat 8 and that's on February
Apache Tomcat 8，即二月份
11th registration for that is open so if
第十一次注册是开放的，所以如果
you'd like to just a few like to join
您只想加入一些
the event just go to spring that IO
该事件刚到IO
/blog
/博客
and you'll you'll see the posting there
然后您会在那看到帖子
also next month we're going to be having
同样在下个月，我们将要
none other than the spring data lead
除了弹簧数据引线
Project Lead all over gear key and
项目负责人
Thomas dairy mom they're going to be
托马斯奶业的妈妈，他们将成为
talking about spring data repositories
谈论 spring data 存储库
and some best practices around those how
以及围绕这些最佳做法的一些最佳做法
to hook them you know how to how to use
钩住他们，你知道如何使用
things like query DSL etc etc on so that
诸如查询DSL等之类的东西
is going to be on February 18th so we
将会是2月18日，所以我们
would love to invite you to those
很想邀请你参加那些
webinars and hope to see you there
网络研讨会，希望在那里见到您
on today's reporting will get posted to
今天的报告将发布到
spring bio /video which is just a
春天的生物/视频只是一个
redirect to YouTube and we'll post a
重定向到YouTube，我们将发布一个
notice in our atom feed on the spring
注意我们的原子在春天
Iowa blog that the recording of this
爱荷华州博客那个的录音
webinar should should be posted today
网络研讨会应该在今天发布
um so keep an eye out for that um and
嗯，所以要注意那个嗯，
then just as a quick note we have not
然后，作为一个简短的说明，我们还没有
enabled direct HTTP downloads for Spring
为Spring启用了直接HTTP下载
binaries from the spring Iowa website
春季爱荷华州网站上的二进制文件
currently so if you're one of the few
目前，如果您是少数几个
that really needs an HTTP download for
确实需要通过HTTP下载
some reason um there is a there is a
某些原因，嗯，有一个
artifact you can get them from the
您可以从
artifactory server and we just have that
人工服务器，我们只有那个
question occasionally so I thought I'd
偶尔问，所以我想
bring it up and there's a spring
提起它，有一个春天
repository fact I can really kind of
我真的可以
walk you through what's going on
引导您了解发生的情况
but in general we really look forward to
但总的来说，我们真的很期待
hearing your feedback on spring
听到您对春季的反馈
framework for oh and and some of the
哦和一些框架
other things that you're going to
你要做的其他事情
touched on today so please hit us up on
今天感动，所以请打给我们
Twitter it's Frank central um or else
Twitter是Frank中央大学，否则
we're on social media etc and let us
我们在社交媒体等上，让我们
know what you think we'd love to hear
知道您的想法我们很想听听
your feedback thanks everyone
您的反馈感谢大家
and your Ian if you have any closing
还有你的伊恩
comments let's let's do that and then
评论让我们开始吧，然后
say go say goodbye just - thanks
说走就说再见-谢谢
everyone for your attention and have a
大家的关注，并有一个
great experience trying spring from the
从春天尝试春天的丰富经验
port of one first for the dough that one
一个第一的面团
once it comes out on Monday and if there
一旦星期一出来，如果有
are any issues in your migrations there
那里的迁移有什么问题吗
is no interior we're really there to
没有内饰，我们真的在那里
help you
帮你
thanks hi everyone
谢谢大家
you
您